Sync & corrections by Costa Dax
www.addic7ed.com
Federal authorities have initiated
a manhunt for William Butcher.
It's Vought. It's a fucking coup
from the inside.
I know who killed Raynor.
Something to do with the Supe terrorist
smuggled into Jersey.
Her brother.
I just want me wife back.
Bring Langley the terrorist
and you'll have her.
I was told he would never
know about Ryan or me.
That was the deal.
You need to make him leave.
Because if you don't,
I'm gonna take Ryan
and I'm gonna run.
Superheroes are not born,
but made, via Compound V.
We got a Supe terrorist below deck
and shit could go sideways just like...
Ah, fucking diabolical!
I said he was mine.
You snooze, you lose, Gramps.
Our newest hero,
Stormfront, stopped the terrorist
before he could take
more innocent lives.
Communication is everything.
Steve and I had been
dating for two years
when he asked me to marry him.
At the rehearsal dinner, my dad said
we should look into a
529 account for our kids.
Steve laughed and said that was nuts
and that we were never having kids.
Which was, um, news to me.
Yeah. Long story short, um,
the caterer was totally
cool with everything,
but the Marriott did keep our
deposit on the banquet room.
So... Yeah.
Communication.
...details are still emerging
about the Supe terrorist
whose senseless attack
on an apartment building
left 59 people dead
and over 100 injured.
His name? Kenji Miyashiro,
a Japanese expatriate
living in the Philippines.
Miyashiro was radicalized
by the extremist group
Shining Light Liberation Army.
Witnesses who caught
a glimpse of the killer
described him as
dead-eyed and unemotional
as he rampaged through
the apartment building
- killing indiscriminately.
- It wasn't your fault.
Many of the 59 victims have
not yet been identified...
Kimiko, look at me.
...to notify their families.
Look at me.
Investigators have so far not disclosed
further details about the attack,
but officials have announced
they will hold a press
conference later this week.
I-I didn't mean to.
I'm sorry. I was just...
No one can debate
that New Yorkers owe their lives
to the brave actions
taken by Stormfront.
Earlier today, Stormfront
made an appearance
at a New York City park.
How many more people have to die?
You guys, I have been shouting
up and down the hallways at Vought,
and you know what they're
doing to stop another attack?
Jack [BLEEP].
Let's show Vought what they have to do.
Tomorrow morning, Vought Square.
Be your own hero. Make your voice heard.
I am counting on you to show us the way.
Don't let me down.
There you are.
I was beginning to worry.
I've missed you...
...so much.
Are you thirsty?
My good boy.
I ever tell you about
my recurring dream?
I'm on stage, alone, at Carnegie Hall.
The audience is made up
of every poor bastard
who got killed by the superheroes.
What are they doing?
Nothing. They're all just watching me.
Waiting for me to do something.
We hit a dead end on Raynor.
I'm sorry.
Christ, I don't want to hear sorry.
Sorry's not an option.
We can't have anonymous
skull-exploding assassins
walking around.
What if they hit the speaker next?
Or the president?
Liberty?
You mentioned her before.
Second-tier Supe, active in the '70s.
She was all over Susan's private server.
Get Marvin to talk to this Liberty.
Address on the back. North Carolina.
All right.
We'll see what we can find.
Wait.
I found Becca.
Or, at least, our best
guess where she is.
Vought facility, armed to the teeth.
Won't be easy.
We had a deal. I didn't come through.
Jesus, Butcher, I'm
just giving it to you.
It's my fault you stopped
searching for her.
I put a target on Homelander's back
and pointed you right at him.
I didn't know Becca was still...
It'd be good to have one less person
in that audience staring at me.
Hey!
See?
You get disrespected
over and over and over,
that's what happens.
I mean, how much shit
is he supposed to take?
Everybody respects you.
Fucking terrorist was my save, not hers.
It was mine.
What? Now that-that media
whore i-is the face of the Seven?
- No, she's not. No, you are.
- Come on.
And it's not just her,
it-it's the entire team.
- No.
- Yes, it is.
It-It's a whole chain of weak links.
I-It's very hard not
to take it personally.
Oh, I know.
I know.
I'll tell you one thing.
- You wouldn't put up with this shit.
- Mm-mm.
One little raise of the eyebrow,
and you would've knocked them
- all back in line.
- Yeah.
God, I miss that about you.
You don't need me to do that.
The Seven is your team.
You nurtured them, you
watered and fed them.
- That's... I did.
- Yes,
and if they can't respect that or you,
well, it may be time
to tear out the weeds
and start all over again.
Change back. Change back!
I'm sorry! I can only
hold a shape for so long
before it really hurts.
Change the fuck back now, Doppelganger!
Yeah, it's okay. Come here.
It's all good.
Oh, my little boy. Come on.
Okay.
It's okay.
I love you.
You're the most powerful
man in the whole wide world.
And there's nothing that you cannot do.
Storming an off-the-books
Vought compound alone?
Butcher, how is it possible that
you're dumber than you look?
- Mate, it's Becca.
- No shit.
But win or lose, you ain't coming back.
Course I am.
That's bullshit.
Look, it's not like Vought's
gonna let us settle down in Orlando.
We got to get gone and stay gone.
What about us? Hmm?
We're the Spice Girls, right?
You're in charge now.
Mazel tov.
Motherfucker, I don't
want to be in charge.
Matter of fact, I don't
even want to be here.
I gave up my family for this.
For you.
When do I get them back?
You find this Liberty slag.
See what you can rumble.
You jump through a few
hoops for the colonel,
and she'll help you the
same way she helped me.
She always liked you more, anyway.
And what about Frenchie?
He's been high as kite for days.
- He won't even notice I'm gone.
- Hmm.
And Hughie?
Kid's a weeper.
Don't want him to get
snot all over me jacket.
Hey, Homelander.
Maeve begged me
to spare your life.
So I gave you a second chance,
and... you failed me.
What are you talking about?
No more lies.
You go ahead and scream.
As much as you want.
What... what did I do?
I told you to kill Hugh Campbell,
and you hesitated.
I-I said that we should
go to the police.
You disobeyed my orders
because you're with him.
Fuck you.
Hughie Campbell broke my fucking heart.
Worse than anyone ever has.
And part of me wants to
blast his fucking face off,
so no, I'm not "with him".
But if you want to kill me
because I'm not a murderer
and I won't straight-up execute someone,
then go ahead.
So, tell me,
am I lying?
You're not lying.
Ooh.
Black Noir. Hi.
Would you like an Almond Joy?
Um, do you mean William Butcher?
Okay.
Well, he was definitely on
the yacht with the terrorist.
Some of his known accomplices were, too.
We lost him in these storm tunnels.
So, yeah.
There you go.
I'll keep you posted when we find them.
Or I can look right now.
Just, uh, run a facial
recognition search.
Or you can join me.
Hey.
- Thanks for coming.
- Hey.
- Oh, you're so bruised.
- Oh, no, it's fine. It's okay.
That was all me?
It's cool. Really.
I mean, you know, chicks dig bruises.
You know, I was in...
When I was in fifth grade,
I took a tetherball to the face.
And Amy Burtenshaw, she brought me
Jell-O Pudding Pops
for, like, two weeks.
I'm talking way too much.
I could've killed you.
But you didn't.
Um...
I got your voice mail.
Oh, God. Can... Oh, God.
Can we just chalk that
up to a-a drunk dial?
I-I'm okay, really, it's just, uh...
Do you just mind, you mind
- if we just don't talk about it?
- Okay.
So, we got the Compound V out there,
and Vought is still kicking,
so we risked our lives
just to make the world way worse.
Yeah, but no, no, no. That's not true.
I mean, you know, these things, they...
Look, Annie, they take time.
How much time?
Just...
Sorry, just give me one second.
Um... Hey, M.M.
Raleigh? Like, the one
in North Carolina?
Yeah, okay, okay.
Jesus, I was just asking.
Um, yeah. Yeah.
Um, just pick me up
at, like, 81st and-and
Central Park West.
Okay, okay, all right.
Um, I have to go.
What's going on?
Can I call you later?
Are you just gonna...
hang out?
Here?
Yeah, I...
I just... I can't go back
to the Tower right now.
Why? What happened?
I can't...
I can't do this anymore.
Are you fucking insane?
She can't come with us,
Hughie. She's chipped.
So, I have a second cousin
who lives around there.
I could tell Vought
that I'm going to visit.
And we'd be out of the city,
away from the cameras.
I mean, no one would see us.
No. Even her standing here is dangerous.
Maybe he's right. I...
This is a bad idea.
If we're gonna go knock
on some Supe's door,
don't you think it makes
a little bit of sense
for us to have one of our own?
Look, she's in rough shape.
She needs this.
You mean you need this?
Hey. How you doing? Cool.
What's up, man?
Oh, fuck!
Don't bullshit me,
- Ashley.
- Shockwave is just here
to talk about Vought for Tots.
I swear to God.
What the fuck is Vought for Tots?
It's a new fitness
outreach for toddlers.
Apparently, they're getting obese.
Well, shit, I fucking
love fat kids. Use me.
Oh, good, you're here.
You tell him yet?
Tell me what?
I thought we were gonna
have a strategy meeting.
A-Train, you're out.
Out of what?
Out of the Seven.
You did great, but we're going
in a different direction, so...
you're out.
What the fuck?
You just said everything was fine.
You're gonna have a
whole year of parades.
Tribute concerts.
You're gonna hit the talk show circuit.
You're-you're gonna have
your own reality show
on Vought+.
The outpouring of love and gratitude
is gonna be off the charts.
Oh, this is bullshit!
You used to get my fucking coffee!
Oh, fuck this. I'm not going.
A-Train... you can't run.
Yes, I can run.
- I just... I-I just...
- Buddy?
You think I don't know
what's been going on?
It's your heart.
I doubt you're even
cracking the top 20 anymore,
and that makes the Seven...
me... look pretty ridiculous.
I do want you to know, though,
this was really hard for me.
Okay?
It's nothing personal.
Uh, we'll always be friends and, uh...
Et cetera.
Attaboy.
Does anyone mind if I put on some music?
Yeah.
- ♪ Defended by our heroes ♪
- Oh, God.
- ♪ You stood among the best... ♪
- You have a really good voice.
You can do that, like, wavering thing
they do on American Idol.
Vibrato.
- ♪ And thanks... ♪
- You've got to be kidding me.
- No. No.
- ♪ From the stars. ♪
♪ It was always burning since
the world's been turning ♪
There it is. Yep.
♪ We didn't start the fire ♪
♪ No, we didn't light it,
but we tried to fight it ♪
♪ Birth control, Ho Chi Minh,
Richard Nixon back again ♪
♪ Moon shot, Woodstock,
Watergate, punk rock ♪
♪ Begin, Reagan, Palestine ♪
♪ Terror on the airline ♪
♪ Ayatollah's in Iran ♪
♪ Russians in Afghanistan ♪
♪ Wheel of Fortune, Sally Ride ♪
♪ Heavy metal suicide ♪
♪ Foreign debts, homeless vets,
AIDS, crack, Bernie Goetz ♪
♪ Hypodermics on the shores,
China's under martial law ♪
♪ Rock and roller cola wars,
I can't take it anymore. ♪
Hey, hey!
This ain't no little
Vegas road trip, okay?
Y'all ain't on no date, either.
Just... chill.
I'm not your goddamn chaperone.
They say if you love someone,
you should set them free.
But that seems crazy to me,
because if you love someone,
you will never let them go.
Never.
Have you heard of the Lovers of Valdaro?
They were alive, like, 6,000 years ago,
and they were found
in this tomb in Italy.
These two skeletons with
their arms around each other.
That's love.
Open up the door.
Bonjour.
You smell like a wet dog.
Oh, you want a drink?
Mm-mm.
Whoa. Who says I'm alone, asshole?
So... are you gonna
tell me what's wrong?
Or you just gonna stain my clean sheets
with your sweaty despair?
I tried to kiss her.
Kimiko?
Her brother died.
I wanted to make her feel better.
You thought a kiss would
make her feel better
or you feel better?
She was in pain. I wanted to help.
You always want to help.
So?
You think
that by saving her,
you can make amends
for all the people you hurt.
For those children
that Lamplighter burned.
- Okay.
- You don't know anything.
Look, she's not a kitten up a tree.
Just leave her alone. Hmm?
Let her grieve.
What good does grieving
all alone ever do?
And in our continuing coverage
of the recent revelations
over Compound V,
protesters all over the Middle East
have taken to the streets demanding...
- Thank you.
- I'll be right back.
Meanwhile, at the United Nations,
governments from all over the
world have voiced their anger
at the Compound V revelation.
- Mm.
- Today, Russia and China
referred to the superheroes as
weapons of mass destruction
and accused the United States
- of terrorism...
- Mm.
You two want a room?
You and the doughnut.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
It's just, um,
my mom never let me have this stuff.
- Hmm.
- It's just... weight gain
in our household
was a capital crime.
But my dad, um,
he'd take me to Dunkin' on the sly.
And he would get me a
chocolate cream-filled doughnut,
and he'd ask me to
tell him about my day.
And he'd... he'd listen.
Baskin-Robbins.
Every Sunday after church.
My pops, he'd always ask
for samples.
Now, this place had 31 flavors,
and that man would taste
each and every flavor
every time we'd go up in there.
There'd be a line all
the way out the door.
People would be mad as hell. Yelling.
Cussing. "Yo, my man,
get your fucking ice cream and bounce!"
You think that stopped him?
Hell, nah. He would stand right there
and order another sample.
"Can I please try the Jamoca
Almond Fudge, please?"
My ass was so embarrassed.
I'd be sitting there, wishing the floor
would just open up and
just swallow me whole.
Man.
Course, now I'd give a year
off my life just to be able
to see that man going
through spoon after spoon
just one last time.
When did he...
16 years ago.
To fathers and sugar.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa. Are you dry wiping?
Am I what?
Come here.
Listen, any part of your body,
- and I mean any part...
- Mm-hmm.
When you dry wipe, you're
not cleaning anything.
You're just smearing
shit all over your skin.
Here. Got to use wet
wipes. There you go.
- You just carry these around with you?
- Damn right...
No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, please!
They're hurt!
- They need help!
- No, please. No, no, no.
This is not the time to be a Supe.
Okay? We're low-key, not with us here.
- Annie?
- I...
There's a ton of people here.
Okay, that guy, he's calling 911.
It'll be okay.
Come on. Come on, we gotta go.
- This was a bad idea.
- Just calm down.
- This was a stupid idea.
- Calm down.
Any place around here without
a million bloody cameras?
Are you okay?
- Did he hurt you?
- No.
I'm okay, I'm fine.
I thought you were dead.
I stopped looking. I
shouldn't have stopped.
I couldn't call anybody. I can't imagine
what it must've done to you. I'm sorry.
I'm so fucking sorry.
No, you've done nothing wrong.
Look at you.
My girl.
Always.
Billy, it's not safe for you to be here.
If he finds you, he's gonna kill you
and you know that.
Fuck him.
I got out of the last
scrape all right, didn't I?
That was a one-time deal.
What did you say to him?
I said if he hurt you...
I would kill myself in front of Ryan.
And my last words would be,
"Your father did this to me".
He seems desperate for a
relationship with his son,
so it worked once.
Well, it's a good thing
he don't know your tells.
I wasn't bluffing.
I'm gonna get you the fuck out of here.
Yeah, how?
Over the fence, the
same way that I came in.
No, no.
Ryan-Ryan can't climb that fence.
Right.
I saw his-his eyes glow.
I thought he might...
Don't he got no powers?
N-No, I-I mean...
Yes, but I'm not... I'm
not raising him like that.
Hey.
There's a garbage truck.
It comes by the house
every morning at 11:00.
I doubt anyone checks the hopper.
You sure it's not a fucking compacter?
Yes, I'm sure.
Okay.
Then that's the plan.
Yeah, yeah.
I have to go.
They get suspicious
when I'm gone too long.
Wait here, I'll be back.
Okay?
Okay, so, we got two rooms.
There's three of us,
so I guess I'll be, uh...
...bunking with M.M., naturally.
Good choice.
Mmm.
- Is that an Almond Joy?
- Mm-hmm.
Nobody likes Almond Joy.
Jeffrey Dahmer...
That's it, he's the only one.
This in my top three for sure.
What are your other two?
Mm...
Charleston Chew...
and Bit-O-Honey.
Jesus Christ!
Those are the, like,
three worst candy bars
in the history of candy!
That's it, you're-you're sick.
In the brain.
Hey, what's up with M.M.'s OCD?
Wait, what-what OCD?
You know, when he changes lanes,
he taps the steering wheel three times.
He stirs the coffee three times.
The antiseptic wipes... Really?
You haven't noticed any of this?
No, but wow, you're right.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
It's just control over things
he can't control, I guess.
I mean...
I should be the last
one talking about that.
Says the girl who's just
stress-eating all day.
Oh, my God!
That was... I...
Was so good, that was really good.
I enjoyed that.
It's harder than it looked.
Nah.
I think, you know,
actually, I think I went
the other way with the eating.
I think I lost, like, seven pounds.
Mm.
I did not have seven to lose.
Well... oh, I sleep
about four hours a night.
I wish I slept four hours a night.
I mean, I'm too busy
chewing my fingernails
down to the quick.
I don't know, whatever a...
I don't know what a quick is, but...
Here's one.
I walk around the Seven Tower
with this...
knot in my gut.
Just wondering
if Homelander is waiting
around every corner to kill me.
It's like living with a
loaded gun in my face.
Do you feel that way now?
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait.
I got it.
But I still want to see you.
Love is a leap of faith.
Like, my last boyfriend was
obsessed with Ed Sheeran.
Yeah, I know.
But he was obsessed.
"Shape of You", "Galway
Girl", whole catalog.
So, he asked me
to get one of these with him.
Two weeks later, he broke up with me.
I fucking hate Ed Sheeran.
Took you ages to quit.
All them little patches, eh?
Do you want one?
No.
The beard's new.
Fancy it, eh?
Eh, haven't decided yet.
How long you been here for then, eh?
Since I gave birth.
Fucking hell.
How you holding up?
Yeah, you know, you forget about
reading the news or...
going to a restaurant...
smoking pot on the couch
and eating Cheetos.
I just act like, you know,
Carol fucking Brady all day.
It's okay.
You know, Ryan's happy, and...
that's what matters.
You're gonna like him.
He's sweet...
and very smart and...
so kind.
I know you hate kids and all,
but I think that he's pretty...
Oh, no, no, no, I don't,
I don't hate kids.
Just...
I'm not a very good role model, am I?
How have you been?
Oh, you know, all right.
Started a private security company.
You know, weddings, bar mitzvahs...
Bullshit.
Homelander said you were
"a man possessed".
He said you've been
chasing after him for years.
Well, I thought he killed you.
So... yeah.
I've been on a bit of a warpath.
But on the bright side,
I'm sleeping in a basement
beneath a pawn shop in East Flatbush.
I'm sorry.
I never wanted that for you.
What was I supposed to do?
Hmm?
Let him get away with it?
What was I before you?
Nothing.
And you saved me.
And here you've been,
fucking living in this shithole
for all this time,
and I haven't been here for you.
I'm gonna make it up to you.
I'm gonna make it up to you
from now till the day I die,
I swear to God.
Is the supervillain threat real?
Hundred percent.
Very real.
But the Seven will protect you.
That's right, right.
Always listen to Maeve.
She always tells the truth.
And we're grateful every day.
On a related subject, Compound V.
Did either of you know about
it before the news broke?
No. Absolutely not.
Madelyn Stillwell,
she lied to all of us.
Turns out she was a monster.
We're-we're just as hurt
and upset and confused
as everyone else.
Let's talk #HeroesSoWhite.
The numbers are rather startling.
92% of heroes are Caucasian.
African American, six percent.
Latin and Asian, each one percent.
Why doesn't Vought want diversity?
Wow. These are real
hardballs, Maria Menounos.
But check your facts.
Let's, uh, take the Seven, for example.
We've got A-Train. He's a black man.
We got Black Noir. He, um...
Well, he doesn't identify
with any race, really,
so... they're covered.
And... we have a gay hero.
Really?
Who in the Seven is gay?
Queen Maeve.
Mm-hmm. Scoop for you, Maria.
Maeve here is a strong, proud lesbian
with a beautiful girlfriend, Elena.
Hispanic girlfriend.
And I, for one, am so proud of her.
Where's Elena?
What did you do to her?
She's fine.
What did I do to her? I set her free.
And you. You've been living
in the shadows so long,
doesn't it feel good
to be out in the sun?
Hold on.
Me and Elena are just friends.
- Oh. Just friends?
- Yes.
Because, see, I heard you
two talking on the phone,
and it sounded a
little more than friends.
So, I did a little digging,
and imagine my fucking surprise.
Okay.
- We had a relationship once.
- Hmm.
Once. A relationship... "Relationship".
That's such a vague word.
What does that mean to you?
What, long walks in the park?
A shoulder to cry on?
Scissoring each other raw?
I ended the relationship
when I joined the Seven.
When I met you.
Stop fucking lying to me.
I am at my wit's fucking
end with the lies.
We're together.
And you love her?
Hmm.
I see.
Well, best of luck to you both.
Oh, is it so hard to believe that
I want you two to be happy?
And in love?
Honestly, Maeve, I am
really, really happy for you.
And have you seen Vought's
"Saving America" ads?
Don't they make you feel all
warm and squishy and patriotic?
Vought wants you to feel calm and safe
so that you continue to
buy their shitty toys
and drinking their shitty energy drinks
and going to see their shitty movies.
But maybe we shouldn't feel so calm.
Or safe.
One Super terrorist has
already gotten through.
More will come.
And for all we know,
these maniacs could already
have flown over our borders
and be standing next to you,
just waiting for their
chance to kill us all.
So what are we gonna do?
We're gonna sit around
and cross our fingers
that Homelander's gonna save us
when he's not on Maria Menounos?
No!
Or will we demand
that Vought do better?
That our government do better!
What do you say?
No.
Mon coeur, please. You will not survive.
Stormfront! Stormfront!
Marry me, Stormfront!
Let's go home.
- Hello?
- Uh,
hello, um...
I'm Hughie. Is-is there, by any chance,
a woman living here who
used to go by the name
of, um, Liberty?
No.
Okay, we have the right address, right?
Is that...?
- Please leave.
- Miss,
I'm sorry if my friend offended you.
But we just want to ask
just a couple of questions.
Just leave me alone.
I took your damn money,
I signed your damn papers,
and I have kept my mouth shut.
You think we're w...
We're not with Vought.
Okay? We...
We just want to learn
what we can about Liberty.
That's it.
Then y'all are just some damn fools.
It sounds like you know her.
Or knew her.
You're wasting your time.
- Okay?
- Miss, Miss, Miss. Hear us out.
If, after that, you want
us to leave, we'll go.
Go ahead.
My father was a lawyer.
Small-time, very smart. And aggressive.
When I was a kid, something
happened between my family
and Vought, which I'd rather
not talk about, but it was bad.
Now, see, my dad, he believed in the law
and that nobody was
above it, not even Vought.
So he went to work. He
got after their asses.
He had one of those...
Remember those little black typewriters,
manual ones with the keys?
I'd go to sleep at
night to all that noise,
my father banging away at that thing.
Wake up the next morning,
he'd still be hammering away.
All night.
But see, Vought wasn't about
to let this one black man
put his foot on their necks.
Mm-mm.
So they hired teams of lawyers.
Paid off judges.
But my father never gave up.
Till one morning I woke up and...
I didn't hear those keys anymore.
Just found him hunched over
that typewriter, dead at 55.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
I'm not here for your sympathy.
But I am gonna tell you that his
fight got passed down to me.
And I'm gonna make Vought
pay for what they did to him
and, ma'am, from what I gather,
what they've done to you, as well.
I mean... it's been 48 years.
What good is dredging all
this stuff up now gonna do?
Honestly we don't know.
But we still need to hear it.
I tried to get people to listen.
Lord knows, so many times, I tried.
But a little black girl accusing
a white superhero of
murder in these parts?
Yeah.
It was during one of those summer rains
that you just knew was coming
by the smell in the air.
I was 11 years old,
asleep in the back
seat of my folks' Ford.
My brother Myron, he was driving.
What's the trouble, ma'am?
Get out.
Hey.
Your car was involved
in a robbery tonight.
No, it wasn't. I-I had it.
I don't know nothing about any robbery.
Just confess.
Why are you doing this
to me, lady? Ain't you
supposed to be a hero?
I am a hero.
For killing a black
piece of shit like you.
I wanted to go to the police.
But my folks,
they thought it was pointless.
So when that man from Vought,
when he showed up and he offered
us that money, we just took it.
$2,000.
That is what my
brother's life was worth.
Just $2,000.
But y'all have got to promise me
that you won't tell anybody that
I sat here and I talked to you.
Because if that woman finds
out that I opened my mouth,
she's gonna kill me.
Ms. Hunter,
that woman, L-Liberty,
n-nobody's seen her since 1979.
I mean, she's probably dead by now.
Oh, no, no.
I...
Right here.
That's her. Right there.
That's Liberty.
Valerie was just a little girl,
and she said it was raining,
so she could be wrong.
She seemed pretty certain.
Yeah, but if Liberty and
Stormfront are the same person,
then that makes Stormfront,
like, what, like, 70 years old?
- More?
- Yeah, but who knows
what Compound V can do?
I mean, maybe she doesn't age
like a regular person. Okay?
This is the same Stormfront
that just became
- America's favorite two-fisted Supe.
- Mm-hmm.
And might've popped Raynor's
head for getting too close.
- Oh, my God.
- What the fuck is going on?
I didn't know that about your dad.
Sounds like he was a real hero.
I thought so, but...
Nah. He's just a man with a disease.
He passed it down to me,
and if I'm not too careful,
I might end up passing it down to my...
Who the fuck do you think you are?
What, you think I don't see it?
Trying to undermine me, steal my team...
- Hold on a minute.
- Let me tell you right now,
it won't work.
I'm the face of the Seven! Not you!
Me. I still score higher in
every demo that counts.
18 to 34, 18 to 49, 25 to 54,
they all love me.
Well, congratulations.
I mean, this constant need
to be loved by everyone
is kind of pathetic, but, um, yay.
Okay.
Okay. Calm down.
I clearly pushed you
a little far. I'm sorry.
Look, I'm... I'm just trying to help.
Really? How?
By taking what's mine?
Let me tell you something right now:
I built this team from the ground up,
and there is no fucking way that anyone
is gonna take it away from me.
You spent $273 million
on that "Saving America" bullshit,
and I am running circles around you
with five guys on laptops
churning out memes.
I practically pay them
with Arby's gift cards.
You...
You can't win the whole country anymore.
No one can.
So why are you even trying?
You don't need 50 million
people to love you.
You need five million
people fucking pissed.
Emotion sells, anger sells.
You have fans.
I have soldiers.
Look, I know that
you probably won't believe this.
I think that you
are the best of us.
are everything we should be.
You just need a little help
connecting with your audience.
You know, change with the times.
God knows I did.
I don't need help connecting
with my audience.
Thank you.
Okay. Well, just know I'm always here,
door is always open for anything.
You're late. Where's the kid?
Babe, we got to get in the
truck or we'll miss our chance.
I'm-I'm not leaving.
What are you talking
about? Of course you are.
Grab the kid and let's go.
You don't really want
Ryan to come with us.
Of course I do. I said
I'd take him, didn't I?
And I wanted to believe you.
Then believe me. Now come on,
we've got to get a shift on.
Listen, if the three of us leave,
you're gonna find a
way to get rid of him.
I know it.
It won't be in an obvious way,
and it won't be right away,
- but you will.
- No, Becca, no.
Billy, I know you. I know
you better than anybody,
and I saw it in your face last night.
I see it now.
He's a billion-dollar piece
of Vought property.
They are not gonna let him go.
You and me, Becca, you and
me, we've got a chance.
Babe, it's Ryan they care about, not us.
Yeah, and then what?
And then Vought raises him
without a mother, right?
Then we have Homelander all over again,
then there's two fucking
assholes in this world.
We could disappear, all
right? Just start again,
- start a new family.
- I have a son!
He's a fucking Supe freak.
Fuck. I'm... Listen, I...
I'm sorry, I d... I didn't mean that.
Becca.
Becca, please come with me.
You were wrong about
me, do you know that?
You put me on this pedestal,
and the truth is, I never
knew how to save you.
You were always one-one bad day away
from pounding someone
to death in a parking lot.
That's not true.
Billy.
He raped me, and when I
found out I was pregnant,
I went to Vought.
I didn't come to you.
I didn't come to you
because I was scared,
'cause I knew that you'd chase after him
and you would seek revenge and
it wouldn't be good for anybody.
I love you.
But the hate that you carry
and the warpath that you're on,
it started so long before me.
I can't.
Becs, I'm not leaving without you.
You have to go, please.
Every guard in this goddamn place
is gonna be here in 60 seconds.
You have to go.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, shit.
- Small token of the trip.
- Mmm.
You know, John Wayne Gacy
used to give those out to kids
when he was a birthday clown.
Whatever, I still love them.
Thanks for letting me come.
It was fun
- until it got so horrible.
- Yeah.
What can I say? It's my specialty.
Well, um,
listen, if you're ever in the
mood for another Almond Joy,
just-just shoot me a text.
That came out so gross. I'm sorry.
Hughie...
we can't do that again.
No, no, no, no. No, we can't.
Why, though?
I mean, th... this is... this is good.
But that's just it.
I mean, we can't afford to
feel good or to feel safe
or to let our guard down.
You can't go through this on your own.
We're all alone.
That's the truth.
But it doesn't have to be like that.
Goodbye, Hughie.
I believe the secret
to a great relationship
is to be willing...
to do anything for your man.
Anything.
I'm a feminist,
but I'm also very sexual,
and I don't see that as contradictory.
What's wrong with giving pleasure
and receiving it?
Thank you for coming in, Gianna.
Yeah, we appreciate your candor.
Thank you so much.
Anytime. It was really
great meeting you.
Really great.
So great.
Bye.
Her. Gianna. I choose her.
I mean, she's the one, no question.
No, she isn't.
Wait, what?
She was, like, hands down the winner.
It was not even a contest.
It's Cassandra.
Cassandra? The one...
the one with the hair
and the creepy skeletons
hugging each other story?
Yes.
That's your wife.
Oh... But...
but I thought I got to choose.
You do, and you're choosing Cassandra.
Congratulations.
Yeah, but, I mean, Gianna...
Is lovely. She's lovely. She's a
valued member of the Collective,
but this marriage isn't about
satisfying your base desires.
It's about rehabilitating your image
and getting you back in the Seven.
That is what you want, isn't it?
There you are.
I was beginning to worry.
Oh, I missed you.
Are you thirsty?
Want some?
Aw, I want you so bad.
Are you okay?
Would you like me to be someone else?
I can be whoever you want.
No.
I don't need anyone...
...but myself.
Like what you see?
See how hot you are?
Hmm?
Come on.
How much do you want this?
How much?
I'm gonna suck your
cock so fucking hard,
so good,
and you're gonna look in
your own eyes when you come.
It's not even gay
if it's with yourself, right?
Oh,
you're so special,
the most special man
on the planet.
Everybody loves you.
Everybody.
Their love
is your strength.
You're pathetic.
I don't need everyone to love me.
I don't need anyone.
I don't
need you!
Sync & corrections by Costa Dax
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net