Sync & corrections by Costa Dax
www.addic7ed.com
Okay, this is insane.
We need more Compound V!
- Absolutely.
- We need more Supes!
More Supes! More Supes!
More Supes! More Supes! More Supes!
Come with me.
What are you doing here?
But on the bright side,
I'm sleeping in a basement
beneath a pawnshop in East Flatbush.
We never wanted that for you.
We all just have Ryan's
best interests at heart.
I want us to be a family.
They just flew me up and showed me.
This house is fake, the
neighbors are fake, you're fake.
No, Ryan!
You have five minutes to
make your opening st...
There's a supervillain
on your school campus.
You hear the calls of distress.
You witness a violent
display of superpowers.
What do you do?
I'm Sheriff Ed Flanagan,
and I'm here with Homelander
to talk about school safety.
On the first report of
an active supervillain,
a hero will immediately
rush to your campus.
But to stay alive in
the moment, remember,
stay calm and follow the law.
Lock all doors and windows.
Arm yourselves.
Your teacher should have
an authorized firearm.
But use whatever you can.
And wait for a hero.
Unfortunately,
the possibility that you will experience
a supervillain attack grows
more likely every day.
But by having an action plan,
you can dramatically increase
your chances of survival.
And survival is all that matters.
- Jody, where's my flag pin?
- How should I know?
Well, I can't go to this
thing without a flag pin.
Bob, before he makes any decisions,
- just let me talk to him.
- One,
the president doesn't like you.
He used the word "standoffish".
And, two, he's decided.
He's declaring a national emergency,
bypassing the FDA,
and authorizing Compound V
for use by law enforcement
- and first responders.
- Wait, Robert.
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- I wish I were.
Doses are going for five million a pop.
Pentagon's got a big order in,
and ICE is next in line.
You can't release V into the mainstream.
We're talking an avalanche
of Supes; it's suicide.
In one hour, I will be standing
at the memorial service
for the fallen heroes
of the House attack,
with my flag pin,
giving my thoughts and
prayers, and pledging
to keep America safe.
The best way to do that
is with Compound V.
Yeah, we know. We were there. Remember?
Covered in my chief of staff's brains.
Look, there was no
terrorist. It was Vought.
It's a fucking coup.
- A bunch of their guys died, too.
- To cover their own tracks.
For the record, I agree with you.
And I hate this.
But you've got no proof.
Folks are scared.
If Vought took a shit in
the middle of Fifth Avenue,
they'd throw a ticker-tape parade.
- Here's what we do have, Bob.
- Oh, let me guess.
A tape of me fucking my kids' nanny
at her daughter's quinceañera?
Release it. Please. I'm begging you.
A plum gig at Fox, and this
shithole in my rearview?
Sounds dreamy.
Okay, what if we got
hard proof? A witness.
Anything.
If you could get Jesus Christ himself,
or maybe Homelander in
front of a camera, sure.
I really am sorry.
I'm nervous about driving in the city.
You'll be okay.
- The plan again?
- Okay,
drive straight to Gen's in Sedona,
cash for gasoline, no hotels.
I don't want to leave you here.
I'll be fine.
The anxious boy? Really?
With the moist handshake?
- Mom, come on.
- Okay. Okay.
Um...
you need a new one.
I...
I'm not gonna wear it.
I don't care if you wear it.
I just want you to have it.
I love you.
I love you, too.
You be safe.
Okay.
Hey.
- What's going on?
- They've lost their minds.
The RPG releases an
electromagnetic pulse on impact.
Should cut through
Stormfront's plasma bolts.
How sure are you?
It's a guesstimate.
So that's Stormfront.
And thanks to Starlight,
we know that Noir
needs only a fuckin' tree nut.
How about A-Train?
Got enough epinephrine here to blow up
that motherfucker's heart.
Hey, we can't just kill everyone.
That is exactly what we're gonna do.
Listen, you heard Mallory.
She said all we need is another witness.
Wile E. Coyote.
Always chases Roadrunner,
always with an elaborate
plan, always fails.
You know, I always say,
"Why do this, Coyote?
All you need is an AR-15,
and 'meep-meep' no more".
Exactly. See?
We're just gonna shoot
Roadrunner in the fucking head.
That won't stop Vought.
That-that won't stop Compound V.
If you kill these Supes,
then Vought's just gonna
make a thousand more.
Yeah, and we're gonna
top those cunts, too.
Great.
So that's settled. We're just
supervillains now, huh?
Vought attacked the country, Hughie.
Fuck 'em all.
What if I testify?
Escaped convicts don't
have a ton of credibility.
No, but maybe I know someone who does.
Give us the day.
Hughie?
See you later.
Officials are still trying to
determine the perpetrator
of the capital attack, the
Department of Homeland Security
has issued a crimson terror alert.
In Washington, all
government buildings...
- How's Noir?
- Unresponsive.
They don't think there's brain damage,
but apparently it's hard to tell.
So, Noir's a vegetable,
Lamplighter's a charcoal briquette,
Starlight's in the breeze
somewhere, and you're,
- what, fine with it?
- Yes.
Because none of that matters
anymore because of this.
So far, no terrorist group
has claimed responsibility.
All right, so,
you didn't do this.
I wish I'd killed Vogelbaum.
- But no, it wasn't me.
- Right.
And there's no supervillains
on American soil.
- None that we know of.
- And that means...
...it's Edgar.
Maybe. I mean, he is pretty smart,
especially for his kind.
...Compound V to members of the military
and law enforcement.
Hey, smile.
This is good news.
Yes, there have been sacrifices,
but we are this close
to no more premieres or paparazzi,
or screaming fans, or any
of that dancing monkey shit.
We have to make sure that
the right people get the doses,
but it is a whole new world.
What about the wrong people?
Couple of billion of them.
They're not just gonna sit there.
Don't worry, silly.
Frederick had a solution for everything.
Okay,
there's something really important
that I've been meaning to ask you.
Last I checked, you
are not 57 years old,
so, come on, why is it
always, always Billy Joel?
I'm 57 on the inside.
No, really. Please.
It was just the music
in my house growing up.
You know, I did some somersaults
to "You May Be Right"
that were pretty thrilling to watch.
♪ Only the good die young... ♪
Butcher is right, you know.
We've already tried to take
Vought down the right way.
This isn't gonna work; this is
not gonna stop Compound V
- from getting out there.
- So it's hopeless?
Just kill 'em all, let God sort 'em out?
I mean...
Then why are you even helping me?
Why did you save me at the Tower?
They were... they were gonna hurt you.
Yeah, but, Hughie, you could
have gotten yourself killed.
I mean, after the way
that I treated you,
you had every reason to give up on me.
So why didn't you?
♪ Only the good die young... ♪
I just... would never.
That's why I'm helping.
You were stupid to text.
Everyone's looking for you.
Where's Elena?
This is the guy?
Uh, I'm sorry...
Hi. Hughie.
He's even more of a
twink than in the photo.
I could split that shit
like dry firewood.
Big fan.
I need to ask you something.
It's a lot.
- I need you to testify.
- Testify?
On the record.
Against Vought, against Homelander,
Stormfront, everything.
Why would I do that?
Because things are really bad, and...
...you're our last chance.
- Pass.
- Look, I get
- that it's dangerous.
- It's suicide.
But that's not the reason.
Well, then, what is?
I'm tired.
We're all tired.
But they're hurting people.
And sooner or later, they're
gonna hurt someone you love.
Am I talking to you?
Look.
I get that it's easier to just disappear
inside of yourself.
Trust me, it's all I want to do.
But we can't, Maeve.
We can't.
This is a war now,
- and we...
- Shut the fuck up.
Christ, you...
Haven't I done enough for you?
Didn't I save your fucking life?
It doesn't matter what
we do, nothing changes.
Nothing ever changes or gets better.
And I'm tired.
Just leave.
Go! Take your fucking twink
and get the fuck out of here!
Okay.
Come on.
Monsieur Charcuter, we need you.
Now.
He said he lives under a
pawnshop in East Flatbush!
- He has to be here.
- Hey. Let her in.
Fucking help me... Billy.
They took him.
They have Ryan.
Who's got him?
I appreciate you coming
all this way, Stan.
Well, I can't exactly be seen
with you at the Tower now, can I?
- Fresca?
- No.
Thank you. Awful stuff.
So, you've had a chance
to look over our proposal?
He publicly confessed to
a sexual assault, Alastair.
And we've made a substantial investment
in the Deep's rehabilitation.
Our internal research bureau
shows an impressive Q rating.
He's an asset to Vought
in these troubled times.
Oh. What sort of commission is
the Church getting these days?
40%? 50?
Sounds like you're
open to reinstatement.
That's fantastic.
What about A-Train?
You do need a speedster,
since Shockwave exploded.
Harder sell.
One has-been back is redemption.
Two is weakness.
Stormfront has problems with him.
And at the moment,
I have to indulge her.
What's her problem with A-Train?
I understand that she was
among your grandfather's
first followers back when
the Collective was a start-up.
I can neither confirm nor deny that.
Then your internal research
bureau knows exactly
what Stormfront's
problem is with A-Train.
Deep is still a win.
Shall I have Business Affairs reach out?
- Please do.
- Let me walk you out.
Sons of bitches.
Okay, yeah.
Voilà. Uh, jambon-beurre.
Simple, but it's the
ingredients, you know?
- Thank you.
- Diet Coke
with Lime, right?
Uh, yeah. Yeah.
We've heard a lot about you.
Uh, I'm sorry, I-I wish
I could say the same.
Uh, you all close with Billy?
Yeah.
I mean... sure.
- Why the hesitation?
- Well...
Let's just say he ain't really
close to a lot of people.
You know? Well, except you, of course.
I'm close to him.
- I am.
- All right, all right, lads,
let's give her some air, eh?
Yeah.
So, Ryan ain't on any
of their social media,
which is good on one hand,
but it don't help us none.
- So, you think he's in the Tower?
- Not sure.
You stay here.
Rest up. I'm gonna go
do a little digging.
Hey, Billy.
I'm sorry, okay?
I have no right to ask you to help me
after what I said to you, but...
Look, don't you worry, all right?
I will find your son.
Thank you.
Fuck off, you lot.
What is it, Samantha?
Mr. Edgar, normally,
I wouldn't put this through,
but the man says
it's life or death, and you'd know him.
What's his name?
William Butcher.
Hi, hi.
We've been having a
super fun time in here.
I've just been googling all the
names of the cats in "Cats".
Can you believe Ryan
has never seen "Cats"?
What happened to your hair?
- Oh, nothing.
- Hey, buddy.
Sorry we had to leave you all alone.
Dad's work can sometimes
get pretty crazy.
He hasn't been alone.
I've been here. I got him
all these dipping sauces.
You didn't want to play
"Vought Tournament of Heroes"?
I'm the main guy.
I was working on my states.
- Uh, states?
- Well, yeah, I write down all 50 states
as fast as I can in
either alphabetical order
or geographical order.
You're giving yourself homework?
Well, Mom says that
learning is a gift, so...
Mm-hmm. That mom of yours,
she sure does have
some cute little sayings.
Do you think maybe I could call her?
Uh...
Hey, Ryan.
Ugh.
I get it. I would feel lonely,
too, if I was cooped up
all day by myself in this
West Elm Death Star.
- Mm-hmm.
- How about
we take a field trip?
What do you say, Dad?
Welcome to Planet Vought.
Have a super day.
Let's give a warm hero's welcome
to Kashden, who's turning five today.
Welcome to Planet Vought.
Would you like to try our new
Brave Maeve Rainbow Veggie Burger?
Holy shit.
There you go, Maestro.
- Pretty cool, huh?
- Yeah.
Hey.
Wait until you try the
Big Homey with bacon.
It's so good.
And-and the, uh, and
the Mocha Noir Shake?
It's amazing.
And it won't be lumpy like your mom's.
Homelander?
Hey.
- Can I get a selfie?
- Ask the boss.
Kidding. Of course you can.
- Of course you can.
- Stormfront? I-I love you.
- Can I get a self... a selfie?
- Oh, sure.
One at a time.
- Homelander.
- Kids first.
I'm a huge fan.
- Can I get a picture?
- It's Homelander!
- All right. Hey!
- I love you! Homelander!
- Homelander!
- Hey, guys...
I want to go home.
Hey. You okay?
I want my mom.
Okay, I got you. I got you.
Thank you, everyone. Excuse me.
Thank you. Excuse me. Excuse me.
Stay back, please. Please,
please, please. Just stay back.
Stay back. Thank you.
- New bling?
- Mm-hmm.
Donna got it for me.
Pretty sure she got it at Duane Reade.
Oh, gosh. Moms.
The gift that keeps on giving, forever.
Oh, shit. I'm sorry.
Wh... No, it's-it's fine.
No, no. I'm an asshole
for bitching about my mom
when yours is...
My mom's not dead.
She's not?
Oh, it's just, you never
mentioned her, so...
She left when I was six.
Oh, wow. Shit.
I'm really sorry.
That's where Billy Joel comes from.
She and I, we used to
have these dance parties.
She was, she was fun.
She made awesome Seven
costumes for Halloween.
And, uh, then one day, she just
left and never called again.
Not even a card.
You know, it was like
some silent alarm went off
and she was like, "Well...
fuck them, time to go".
No, I'm sure that that's not it.
What would you call it?
I guess that's why I always
just kind of hang in there,
no matter how bad it gets.
'Cause I...
I-I don't want to be like her.
That's kind of clingy
and pathetic, isn't it?
No. No.
It isn't.
At all.
What's up, shitbirds?
Jesus Christ!
What the fuck?! What the fuck?!
- How did you find us?!
- Please.
I can cover the boroughs
in, like, three hours.
I went looking, that's all.
I'm surprised your heart can take it.
My heart is just fine. Take a
step closer and I'll show you.
Hey, I saved your life,
asshole. And now you're coming after us?
We're even now, bitch.
Holy shit!
Is this true?
Everything makes a little
more sense now, doesn't it?
Where did you get this?
I didn't get it. Okay? I was never here.
You got that shit on your own. Yeah?
But wh... why-why are you doing this?
'Cause I want back in.
So, I need her gone.
Fuck that Nazi bitch.
Would you ask Mario if he could whip up
some of those Gruyère puffs?
Would you like an order?
They're worth the cheat day.
I assume you got a man out
there, with a clean shot?
More than one.
Then I'll skip the
fucking hors d'oeuvres,
if you don't mind, and we'll
just cut straight to it, yeah?
You mentioned on the
phone that you could help
with Homelander's son.
I must say, I'm not sure what you mean.
That boy is your only
possible contingency
against Homelander.
Now, that contingency don't work
if they're off playing
Ward and the Beav.
I can fix that.
Thank you, Alvin.
Homelander's a friend.
Why would I betray him?
Because you're a ruthless bastard.
That's hurtful.
You turned a racist piece of shite
into America's sweetheart.
What word would you use?
Stormfront's good at
making people angry.
Angry people want Compound V.
Compound V raises our stock price.
Look, I'd have preferred
V remained a secret,
but we play with the cards we're dealt.
It's not ruthless,
it's prices per share.
That's all.
Maybe you should take a
look in the mirror, mate.
'Cause that bitch should bother you.
Of course she does.
But it's not about me.
I can't lash out
like some raging, entitled maniac.
That's a white man's luxury.
So, it's just business, then, eh?
When, Mr. Butcher, in history,
has it ever been about
anything different?
And what makes you think
that you can control that racist bitch?
Look, I've got to get across town...
Look, I can get the boy away
from Homelander, all right?
How?
That's my business.
When I got him, I'll call your people,
they zero in on this cell signal,
and then come and scoop him up.
And then you do a better fucking job
of hiding him this time, yeah?
You have my word.
I will get Rebecca and
Ryan somewhere safe.
No.
Not Becca. Becca stays with me.
But that's the whole point.
That he's raised by his mother.
Find him a new fucking mum.
I'm taking my wife
back. That's the deal.
And what happens when Rebecca
shows up on my doorstep,
begging to be reunited with her boy?
You say it's the only way
you can guarantee Ryan's
protection from Homelander.
'Cause as you know,
a mother will do anything
to protect her son.
And you call me a ruthless bastard.
You tell me where he is...
...and I'll do the rest.
Where's Ryan?
He's, um, he's inside.
He doesn't want to talk.
- So, go in anyway.
- No, no, no, no. I've tried.
He... he wants to be left alone.
You are the strongest man in the world,
and you're scared of a little boy.
He's your blood.
Just talk to him.
Be the man I know you are.
New York. North Carolina.
North Dakota. Ohio.
Oklahoma. Oregon.
I'm sorry.
No, no, no, no. Buddy,
don't you be sorry.
I... I should've known better.
There were just... so many people.
Yeah, there was.
You know, I remember the
first time I was in a crowd.
Probably didn't bother you.
I was terrified.
All these people staring at me
and reaching out, trying to grab me,
and egging me on to use my powers.
I just... I felt like I was... drowning.
Well, what'd you do?
Well, I took off.
I flew away.
They found me 80 miles down the I-9.
Crying my little eyes out.
You? Cry?
Yes.
But I'm a man, so, not
in a long while. But...
who knows, maybe, uh...
maybe next time, you'll fly away.
Maybe... with me.
Look...
I know you want me to be like you.
But, Dad, I'm not.
Son...
I didn't just wake up one
day and fly out the door.
That's not how it works. I had to learn.
Only I didn't have anyone to teach me,
'cause the doctors that... um...
The people that raised me,
uh, were scared of me,
so they kept their distance.
And I had to figure it
all out by myself, see?
Well, you-you don't have
to go through any of that.
I'll teach you.
Really?
I love you.
Hey, did you find anything?
They got him in a cabin up in Rochester.
- What?
- I mean... Becca!
She's great. We-we talked earlier.
And, um, she's-she's
really great. She's...
- You're really... you're great.
- All right, easy, tiger.
How'd you get on? I
guess you got fuck all?
No witnesses. But we
definitely found fuck all.
I'm not sure I'm using that
term properly, but, uh...
here.
Fuck me.
This is a jackpot.
Well done, you two.
This'll do nicely.
All right, listen up, you lot.
Getting the kid back,
it ain't your fight,
and I ain't gonna ask you to come along.
Lick my big black balls, Butcher.
Sorry, Becca.
You done asked us to lie,
spy, do all kinds of
fucked up shit for you.
Now we finally get a chance
to do something good,
and you think we're gonna
take a pass on that?
We're in.
Of course we're in.
All right.
Let's get a shift on.
What?
You remember the range at Fort Bragg?
I was a better shot than you.
Well, you had a bloody
good teacher, didn't you?
I like your friends.
Especially Hughie. He's, uh...
He's good for you.
Look, Becca... you ain't coming with us.
Bullshit.
Ryan doesn't know you,
he'll never come to you.
It's too dangerous, and I
ain't gonna lose you again.
He's my son, and I'm coming.
I need you to promise me something.
I need you to promise me
that you will save him
no matter what and you
will get him back to me.
Yeah. Of course.
You realize this isn't
just about me, right?
Like, h-he can't grow
up like Homelander.
You have to think of all of the people
out there that he would...
Swear to me, then.
You swear to me on your brother's soul.
I swear to you.
I swear to you on Lenny's soul.
- Okay. Okay.
- All right.
I can use your help loading the car.
What if it happens again?
When I see Stormfront...
Stormfront...
...what if I freeze?
"Freeze", yes?
Sorry, I'm still learning.
Look.
If there's one thing I know,
it's that you can take care of yourself.
So when the time comes,
you'll know what to do.
Let's go.
Keep going. You got it.
That's it, don't give up.
That's it, that's it. Keep going.
Little more, little more, you got it.
Oh... hey, that's okay.
You'll get it, you'll get it. Um...
I know what.
Um, imagine, um...
Well, sometimes it helps to
imagine someone you hate. Okay?
So, try that.
But at home,
when I say "hate", I have to
put a quarter in the swear jar.
Well, there's no swear jar here.
So, you can hate away.
But I don't really hate anyone.
Aw, well,
that is very sweet, Ryan.
But it's not something we can afford.
We're under attack.
We are?
Bad guys want to hurt us just
'cause of what we look like.
They want to wipe us from this Earth,
just because of the color of our skin.
Really?
It's called white genocide.
And we're gonna need people
like you to protect our kind.
Hmm. All right.
So, let's try again.
Go for it. Imagine, uh...
You got to be fucking kidding me!
What?
Are you sure this'll work?
Don't worry, it will work.
This is nothing compared to the raves
I used to set up in Algiers.
Do you dance?
Of course I dance.
What is the point of
life without dancing?
She's on the move.
♪ One, two, three, four... ♪
I see her, Frenchie. We got to go now.
- You close?
- Un moment, mon ami.
- Holy shit. It just broke.
- Stunning news coming out of Vought Tower
in New York City, concerning Stormfront
and alleged Nazi ties.
Stormfront may be 100 years old.
What's even more incredible,
we have authenticated photos
showing Stormfront
with Nazi High Command,
including Goebbels and Göring.
Based on the photos, it is now
believed that she was the wife
of Frederick Vought, who
was of course the founder
of Vought International.
Already, an intense international outcry
has emerged, under...
I can't believe I
actually have to say this,
this day and age, but Nazis are bad.
♪ Nazi Stormfront, Hitler's star ♪
♪ Run her over with a car. ♪
It's catchy.
- You ready?
- Oui.
But the question now is how can
we possibly let Vought release
Compound V in light of this
unprecedented malfeasance?
- What's "malfeasance"?
- A Nazi in Seven Tower?
- Uh, it's a...
- Was she part of the attack...
Never mind.
Aah!
- What's happening?
- Don't know.
Stay here.
Now!
Ryan! Hey! Hey.
Hey. Hey. Bud. Hey.
- Mom? Mom...
- It's me.
- Come here.
- Mom, Mom. I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean anything I said.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean any of it.
It's okay.
- We got to go.
- I love you so much.
You're okay. We're gonna
go, okay? Come on.
Who's that?
That's my husband.
It's all right.
Come on.
I got you.
Come on. To the car, this way.
What the fuck?
- Qu'est-ce que c'est ?
- What the hell
are they doing back here?
Butcher, this wasn't the plan.
What's going on?
What's wrong?
Take my car, get them both to Mallory.
Get them both safe.
No, no. That's not part of the plan.
The plan just changed.
M.M., you're the only
one I trust with 'em.
Hey. What's happening? No.
M.M.'s gonna take you
to a woman with the CIA.
What? No, you have to come with us.
I cut a deal with Stan Edgar.
What?
I cut a deal that when I got
Ryan, that I would call Vought.
They were gonna come and take him away,
and that you'd never
fucking see him again.
What?
But fuck me, I-I couldn't do it.
- Bedroom's clear.
- Kitchen's clear.
- All rooms secure.
- Mr. Butcher?
You here?
Did I hear you say "Butcher"?
What's going on?
Do you have the boy?
Where's my son?
Where is my son?!
I'm not... I'm not leaving here
without you. I don't care.
I was gonna sell you out.
I fucking well might do it again.
You didn't, though. You
didn't and you won't.
You can't have a cunt
like me around that kid.
I don't want to pass my shit on to him.
Don't say that. You
have to come with us.
You raise him right.
- You fucking raise him right.
- No. Don't say that.
And I'll make sure they never find you.
Don't you say that! Stop it. Stop.
- You have to come with us.
- Becca, we are out of time.
Please.
You got to let me do this.
You got to let me do
this one fucking thing.
Becca!
There you are, you
slippery little bitch!
I'm assuming it's you who sent
all those lies to the press.
They're not lies.
The pictures are clearly deepfakes,
and you're a lying slut.
Okay.
Come here.
People love what I have to say.
They believe in it.
They just don't like the
word "Nazi", that's all.
Are you all right?
- You all right? Yeah?
- Ryan. Ryan, Ryan.
- Ryan. Ryan!
- Ryan. Come here.
Are you okay? Are you okay?
Go. We'll hold her off.
You're okay.
What about the truth?
What truth?
What is the truth?
And what are you laughing at?
She says the truth is,
she's gonna stick her
boot up your Nazi kitty.
Annie!
Come on, the RPG!
It's in the car! It's our only chance!
Hey, Kraut.
♪ You've got them all by the balls ♪
♪ Causin' waterfalls ♪
♪ Stone walls, bar brawls ♪
♪ Common stalls that cause 'em all ♪
♪ To you they crawl, body sprawl ♪
♪ Smokin' Pall Malls,
close call, stand tall ♪
♪ Doll, you make them feel so small ♪
♪ And they love it... ♪
Eat my shit, you Nazi bitch!
Die, you bitch!
Girls do get it done.
Yeah!
Bitch!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Come here, Ryan.
Not on your life.
You're not like her, Ryan.
You belong with us.
Stay the fuck away from my son!
We love you, Ryan.
You fucking bitch.
Stop! Stop it!
Stop, please. Stop it!
Stop, you're hurting
her. Just let her...
Stop it!
Stop, you're hurting her.
Just let her go.
Let her go!
- Stop!
- Look at me.
I like to see the light go out.
Stop!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Mom.
No. No...
No. No, no, no.
Hold on.
I'm sorry.
Help us!
Somebody help us!
It's not his fault. It's not his fault.
You make sure he knows that.
He, uh...
He's good. He's good.
He's good.
You promise me you'll keep him safe.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I didn't mean it.
Mommy.
Mom.
Mom, please.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry...
Ryan?
Did you do this?
I didn't mean to.
Let's go.
Come here.
Come.
Ryan... Ryan.
Come here.
No.
He's mine.
What, are you gonna blow yourself up...
to save the little shit who
fucking murdered your wife?
I promised.
- Have it your way.
- Stop.
What are you doing here?
You're gonna let them go.
And if I don't?
- Please!
- Don't die with them.
Let them go.
- Maeve!
- You're gonna stop hunting Starlight,
you're gonna leave me and Elena alone...
Take my daughter!
...or I release this.
If you do that...
...I'll destroy everything
- and everyone.
- Great.
As long as everyone sees
what a fucking monster you are.
As long as no one
ever loves you again.
Homelander! Homelander!
Homelander!
Homelander! Homelander...
We believe that Stormfront
was the sole perpetrator of
the attack on Washington.
In the light of Stormfront's atrocities,
the release of Compound V has
been placed on indefinite hold.
Homelander?
Mr. Edgar, we have a follow-up question.
Thanks to the heroism of
Queen Maeve and Starlight,
Stormfront has been neutralized,
and is being held in an
undisclosed location.
I would personally like
to apologize to Starlight,
who was wrongfully accused
of sabotage and conspiracy.
Welcome back to the team.
And I know that you and
Maeve are two of the best,
most loyal friends
that I could ever have.
We are your heroes.
We are here to serve and protect you.
Stormfront's violation of
that special relationship,
of that trust, is unacceptable
and she will be punished.
Justice will be served.
She will be punished.
As the leader of the Seven,
I give you my word,
no one will ever...
Gentlemen, thank you for coming.
Always happy to see you, sir.
I'm afraid we had
an incident at the Archives.
Someone broke in and
stole PDR on Stormfront.
Hmm. PDR?
Private data reserve.
No one saw the thief come or go.
Isn't that right, A-Train?
That was you? Dude.
I didn't know, sir. Fuck him.
- I would never go behind your back.
- Please,
- just let me explain.
- I think it showed initiative.
Stormfront's been critical of
the Church for a long time,
and Vought needs to take a
firm anti-Nazi stance right now.
Wait.
- D-Does that mean...
- I just spoke to Stan Edgar.
You're back in.
- Fuck yeah!
- What? Yeah!
Yeah! A-Train is back, baby!
- Yeah!
- All right!
- Whew!
- Finally!
- Yeah.
I'm back too, right?
Right? I'm anti-Nazi.
I'm sorry, Deep, but
they only had one slot.
One hero is redemption, two is weakness.
So they took him?
Fuck yes, they did!
Well, shit! Peace out, bitch!
Ha ha!
You have to be patient, Deep.
We'll get you into a few more
courses, up to Level Seven.
No, I don't want to pay for
any more fucking courses!
Deep, please calm down.
I signed over my bank account to you.
I filled out all those fucking
children's workbooks!
I married some weirdo who
gives terrible blowjobs!
I-I did everything you asked,
and when I found out that
we're all just fucking space
spores, I didn't laugh.
I did everything you asked.
Because you said you'd
get me back in the Seven.
- You fucking promised.
- I'm sorry, Deep,
but you are acting
like a toxic personality.
I think you should leave.
Fuck Fresca.
Look at you.
I know. I know...
But if Billy Butcher
can do the right thing,
then there's got to be
some kind of higher power.
You know?
Are you sure it's safe for you
to go back into the Tower?
No.
No, I'm not. But...
If you jump ship and you
let the assholes steer,
then you're part of the problem.
- And...
- Hmm.
...someone taught me something
about hanging in there.
I've been thinking about that lately...
the hanging in there.
And I think maybe I am too clingy.
- No, you're not.
- Sticking with people
just because I'm
terrified of losing them?
I-I...
I can't do that anymore.
I think it's time I go off,
stand on my own two feet for once.
Right. Um...
Yeah, no worries. We'll, um...
We'll just be friends, then.
Oh... oh, God, no. No, no, no.
I'm still gonna cling onto
you, I'm not fucking crazy.
So, if you weren't talking about me,
who were you talking about?
I'm scared.
This here...
belonged to your mum.
This is St. Christopher.
She gave it to me a long time ago,
and told me...
it would keep me safe.
And it has.
Mostly.
Now your mum...
is gonna help keep you safe.
Come on.
Now...
remember what I told you.
Don't be a cunt.
William, I'm so sorry.
Vought's gonna want him back.
Let me handle Vought.
You think he'll turn into his father?
Becca didn't think so.
I pray she's right.
All the charges against you and
the Boys have been dropped.
Even for the crimes you did commit.
You're a free man.
And the White House is opening
an Office of Supe Affairs.
Victoria Neuman is the new czar.
She's sneaking me some
off-the-books funding
for a team that can
keep tabs on the Supes.
If you're interested.
♪ I may not always love you ♪
♪ But long as there
are stars above you ♪
♪ You never need to doubt it ♪
♪ I'll make you so sure about it ♪
♪ God only knows what
I'd be without you ♪
♪ If you should ever leave me ♪
♪ Well, life would still go on ♪
- ♪ Believe me ♪
- Where to?
- ♪ The world could show nothing to me ♪
- Dancing.
♪ So what good would living do me? ♪
♪ God only knows what
I'd be without you ♪
I'd be without you... ♪
I can do whatever I want.
I can do whatever...
I want.
I can do...
whatever I want.
♪ What I'd be without you... ♪
I can do whatever the fuck I want!
I can do whatever the fuck I...
want!
Congratulations on the
appointment, Congresswoman.
It's about time we had
an Office of Supe Affairs.
Well, I know it was your intel
that took Stormfront down.
So, thank you.
Yeah, and that's just the start.
We have enough dirt
to ruin a dozen Supes.
Be a death blow for Stan Edgar.
That is, of course,
if you're open to, uh, expediting
the Church's tax-exempt status.
Small price to pay.
Call my office, set up a meeting?
You are one of the good ones, Vic.
- See you soon.
- See you.
Hi.
- Here's the research you asked for.
- Thank you.
- And your 2:00 is waiting.
Hugh Campbell.
I don't know how to repay
you for what you did.
- You know, I can think of a way.
- Oh?
You can... give me a job.
You serious?
Uh, what about your team?
Don't get me wrong, I-I-I still
want to fight Vought, I just...
I want to do it the right way.
Not covered in quite as many guts.
Look, the truth is,
I never totally fit in with the guys.
And... I think it's time I
stand on my own two feet.
- They know you're here?
- I haven't told them yet.
When can you start?
♪ Come out, Virginia,
don't let me wait ♪
♪ You Catholic girls
start much too late ♪
♪ Aw, but sooner or later
it comes down to fate ♪
♪ I might as well be the one ♪
♪ Only the good die young ♪
♪ That's what I said ♪
♪ You might have heard I run
with a dangerous crowd ♪
♪ We ain't too pretty,
we ain't too proud ♪
♪ We might be laughing a bit too loud ♪
♪ Aw, but that never hurt no one ♪
♪ So come on, Virginia, show me a sign ♪
♪ Send up a signal,
I'll throw you a line ♪
♪ The stained-glass curtain
you're hiding behind ♪
♪ Never lets in the sun ♪
♪ Darling, only the good die young ♪
♪ Whoa, baby ♪
♪ I tell ya, only the good die young ♪
♪ Only the good die young ♪
♪ Aw, she never cared for me ♪
♪ But did she ever
say a prayer for me? ♪
♪ Oh, whoa, whoa ♪
♪ Come out, come out, come out ♪
♪ Virginia, don't let me wait ♪
♪ The Catholic girls
start much too late ♪
♪ Sooner or later it
comes down to fate ♪
♪ I might as well be the one ♪
♪ You know that only
the good die young ♪
♪ Tell ya, baby ♪
♪ You know that only
the good die young ♪
♪ Only the good die young ♪
♪ Only the good die young. ♪
Sync & corrections by Costa Dax
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net