Sync & corrections by Costa Dax
www.addic7ed.com
Holy shit!
We are going to hold hearings
on Vought and Compound V!
I'm the world's greatest superhero.
You're my greatest failure.
I do like you.
You've got spunk.
You're gonna be a big help to me.
What the hell does that mean?
That's fucking Lamplighter.
These people are test subjects.
They're trying to stabilize the V.
Anywhere, anytime, you get a solid Supe.
Why would Vought do that?
We are in a war.
For the culture.
But we can fight back
with an army of
supermen millions strong.
Everyone I have ever
loved is in the ground.
And then I found you.
We found each other.
30% of the public
is hard-core aware now
and know how the system works.
And then we don't do anything about it.
That's why Super terrorists
continue to invade America.
There are illegal immigrants
pouring into this country
every day, and any one of
them could be a Super terrorist.
Many are calling for more
superheroes in order to counter
the Super terrorist threat
and protect Americans.
What is our government doing about this?
- Got to go. I'm late for class.
- Thanks.
- All of us...
- Have a good day, hon.
...we need to stand up right now.
I am sick of waiting for some executive
to finish his racket...
We are going to hold hearings
on Vought and Compound V...
That's $1.45.
I'm gonna tell you something
I probably shouldn't.
that the government doesn't want you...
And they want
more Super terrorists. That's...
Many people are pointing out that
the rush to judgment by the left...
- Victoria Neuman's accusation that...
- No offense.
- I get you have your talking points...
- Have a good day, hon.
...but why does it matter
what some supervillain-loving
snowflake has...
Every minute we waste...
One Super terrorist
has already gotten
through. More will come.
- That's $1.45.
- And, I mean, for all we know...
these maniacs could have already flown
over our borders and be standing next
- to you right now...
- You all right, pal?
- ...just waiting for their chance
- Yeah.
...to kill us all.
Keep America safe
again. And I am so glad
that I was there this
time. But what about...
- I am counting on you.
- Have a good day, hon.
Every minute we wait...
No, it's up to us.
We have to make our voices heard.
I am counting on you
to show us the way.
Don't let me down.
Hey.
Whoa. Whoa, whoa.
I saw the light in your eyes.
- Just-just take the money.
- You one of them?
- You a fuckin' supervillain?
- What?
- Are you a bulletproof motherfucker?!
- No. Please.
I have a family. Please.
♪ What a wonderful world ♪
♪ What a wonderful world. ♪
Look, I told you.
Stormfront gave the orders.
I just executed them.
It was, um...
- It wasn't easy.
- Yeah,
I think we can all agree that
you're the real victim here.
Now, let's cut the shit
and go over it again.
- From the start.
- I had just left the Seven.
And Mr. Edgar invited me to his club.
Put away that petulant look
- before you hurt someone with it.
- Yeah,
I should be chuffed we're pissin' away
the best asset we ever got our mitts on.
- And your plan would be?
- Same as always.
Squeeze the cunt till he
gives up the next cunt,
then kill the fuck when we're done.
I have no doubt you'd be happy
with that unending cycle of brutality.
How can you not want
blood for what he done?
He's willing to speak against
Vought at the hearing.
We've never had Congress
on our side before.
Congress. Please.
What a bunch of corrupt
fucking cunts they are.
Oh, come on, you're not the first person
to call me a cunt, Mr. Butcher.
I'm starting to think it's
like a... badge of honor.
Term of endearment
where I come from, love.
Mm.
Well?
Opposition's gonna have
a field day with him.
Disgruntled ex-Supe? I am fairly sure
he's fucked half the Sacred
Heart cheerleading squad.
But, yeah, he'll be a good witness.
It's not enough, though.
Not enough? If torturing and burning
a bunch of mentals on Vought's say-so
ain't enough for you muppets,
then what the fuck
are you good for, huh?
- A strongly worded tweet?
- You're a wanted felon, asshole.
- We don't need your help.
- Yes, we do, Lisa.
Mr. Butcher here has fought
Vought harder than we ever have.
But I would like a turn.
If we can... trust each other.
Uh, I think we can.
- Trust each other.
- Hold still.
What do you need?
Okay, we know what they
were doing at Sage Grove,
but we don't know why.
Why test Compound V on patients?
What do they want?
I need the full picture.
If we're gonna take a shot at the king,
we can't fucking miss.
We know someone who
might know the full picture.
Oh, well, that's fucking rich, isn't it?
Who is it?
Like you said...
we're gonna have to trust each other.
Would you like a coffee?
Um, no, thanks.
How 'bout a white
chocolate unicorn frappe?
- They're really good.
- No.
- I'll get one to share.
- Mom, I don't want
a fucking unicorn frappé.
Okay. Sorry.
J-Just nervous.
When did you get to town?
I never left.
I've been staying at
the Days Inn in Newark.
I'm not leaving until we talk this out.
I know what I've done to you.
Believe me, I know.
Mom, it's not just you.
It's...
Do you remember that...
cross that you gave me for confirmation?
Before every save that I went on,
I would touch it.
Like a...
football player leaving a locker room.
I thought that God was
sending me on a mission.
I feel so stupid.
I gave my whole life to nothing.
That's not true.
Mom...
the good guys don't win.
The bad guys don't get punished.
What we do means nothing.
It's just all for money and...
I am in the middle of all of it.
Alone.
Honey, you're not alone.
You're not.
Let's go away,
you and me.
Let's-let's get away from all of this,
get away from Vought.
Escape for a while, hmm?
I cleared it already.
You cleared what?
W-With Ashley at Vought.
You called them?
Y-Yeah, about an hour ago.
- Why?
- Mom,
th-they could be looking for m...
Mom!
Colonel, you think the
congresswoman is in danger?
She has her security detail.
Which will be useless
if a Supe drops in.
She's our best chance to nail Vought,
but only if you keep her
alive until the hearing.
Oui, madame.
And, Serge...
...no abandoning your post this time.
Oui, madame.
Hey.
I'm-I'm all right. I'm coming with you.
You're in no shape to go anywhere.
Besides, we got a very
important job for you.
We need you to look
after our star witness.
Hey.
You guys want to watch
"Deep Does It in the Blowhole"?
You ready to get wet?
I don't want to watch that... film.
It's a classic. You'll love it.
Butcher, let's go.
Hello, Mum.
Hey, Billy,
you ain't been picking up.
Yeah, we're in a meeting.
I-I'm in New York.
Look, I told Judy to tell
you not to fucking come.
Oh. Language.
It's a bleedin' expensive plane ticket.
All right? And I ain't
got the time to just...
Billy, he's dead.
Your father's dead.
You there?
When did that happen?
Can I see you, please?
I need to see you right now.
Let me out!
God.
Please, God.
Please let me out. Please.
Come on, man, stop.
It's not cool.
Guess you should've made your wife come,
snowflake cuck.
You know, you don't need the discs.
You can just download these.
Uh, what do you want to watch next?
Uh, "Translucent: The Invisible Cock".
"Queen Maeve: Pleasure Slave".
Yeah. "Big Black Noir".
Oh. "Starlight Pulls an A-Train".
I'm good. I'm good. Thank you.
Okay.
Different strokes, man.
Please don't say that in this context.
I should just get up and leave.
But you like watching
Homebanger fuck me, don't you?
You know, this isn't healthy, man.
Y-You can't watch porn
while the... sun's out.
Look, if I get up at that
hearing, I'm dead anyway.
What difference does it make?
Okay.
Drop the remote, or I'll
burn your fucking face off.
Uh...
Want me to fuck your wife
like she deserves, cuck?
Did you know I was a prodigy?
A fucking prodigy.
I lit my first fire at four.
Burned my whole house down.
My dad...
he was so proud.
"My son's a Supe".
I was gonna do great things.
I almost did.
Now look at me.
I'm like the cuck in the porn,
sitting on the sidelines
while the real heroes are
out there doing the fucking.
You want to know why they
left me to babysit you?
Because you're useless?
My mom... she, uh...
Never mind.
After... she was gone,
I watched my dad do...
nothing his whole life.
But me...
I thought I'd finally found...
something.
I thought I found what
I was meant to do.
But it turns out I'm...
shit at that as well.
You're not the cuck.
I'm... the cuck.
Actually, you're worse.
You're the cuck fluffer.
Hey-hey!
What's up?
How y'all doing out there?
Good to see you!
- Yeah!
- All right!
Hey, do me a favor.
Who's the real heroes?
You are!
Thank you! I just want to be clear.
No one condones the tragic shooting
at the convenience store.
Our thoughts and prayers go out
to Kuldeep Singh's family.
And we are making a donation
to Samaritan's Embrace in his name.
Absolutely.
Thoughts and prayers.
But...
that doesn't change facts.
This used to be a-a beautiful country.
- Remember?
- Yeah!
One nation under God.
Remember?
Right before these godless,
inhuman supervillains started
pouring across our borders
and dragging us down into their mud.
What do SJWs like Victoria
Neuman want us to do?
Just let 'em in and give
'em a cup of iced tea?
And then punish us
- for trying to stop them.
- That's right.
Has there ever been anyone
in history more persecuted
just for trying to protect their own?
We are at war!
- Yeah!
- We need more Compound V.
- Absolutely.
- Yeah!
- We need more Supes!
- More Supes!
- More Supes! More Supes!
- We need more superheroes!
More Supes! More Supes!
- More Supes! More...
- Now,
I've always been honest
with you... you know that.
And I got to be honest with you now.
It brings me no pleasure
to tell you this,
but we also had a mole in the Seven.
That's right.
One of our own.
Starlight.
I know, I know. It's okay.
She's been apprehended,
and she can't hurt anyone else.
I can't believe this.
Put 'em in. All of 'em.
I want all of 'em in at the same time.
Okay, this is insane.
- Hey.
- No.
Fuck yes...
Starlight has been
conspiring with the people
who murdered, in cold blood,
- my brother...
- Oh, my God, fuck.
...the hero Translucent.
If you are just tuning in...
Um, uh...
- I bet you she's in 42D.
- You have reached
- the voice mailbox...
- Come on, Butcher, where are you?
And that is if she's
still alive, which...
Wait, wait, wait,
- what's 42D?
- At the Tower.
Supe-proof, mostly.
- Steel walls six feet thick.
- How do I get in?
Into the Tower? Yeah, you don't.
And I'm sorry, man, but...
- she's probably dead.
- There's got to be something.
Right? Like a... like a secret entrance?
Maybe one or two, but
forget it, man. It's crazy.
Okay, show me. Come with me.
Look at you. You're still fucked up.
Which is exactly why I need your help.
Get... your... friends.
Butcher isn't picking up,
and the others are
halfway across the state.
We got to go! Now!
Listen, Vought screwed you over, right?
Well, now they're trying to do
the exact same thing to her.
This shit is over for me.
My whole life is over, okay?
This is your last chance
to be a hero again.
Come on, I mean,
do you-you want to be the cuck
or do you want to be the...
guy who fucks the wife?
Okay. Yeah, yeah.
Let's go fuck the wife.
Consensually. Come on, come on.
Hello, Mum.
Will you come with me?
Now, don't hate me.
Why would I hate you?
Look, I'm sorry. It was my idea,
but you wouldn't come any other way.
Look, look, look, look, don't.
- He hasn't got much time.
- Not my problem.
That's yours, 'cause you
stayed with the cunt.
Have I ever asked you for anything?
Ever?
William.
Ah.
What, no hug?
You step one inch closer,
and I'll kill you quicker than
that fucking ass cancer.
I'll bet you would.
I seen on the news where you
topped that Stillwell slag.
It weren't me.
But thanks for your support.
Please, please.
I just want to talk.
Two minutes.
You been following the Ashes?
You want to talk about fucking cricket?
You remember the '83 World Cup?
I took you to every match...
Leeds,
Old Trafford.
You loved it.
Do you know why I loved it?
'Cause you'd get on the
piss with your loser mates.
And I could fuck off for
hours and you'd never know.
Yeah, well, let's not do this then, eh?
Yeah, let's not.
I know I was no perfect father.
But I know I never got a chance
to say goodbye to Lenny.
And I don't want that with you.
Didn't have a chance to
say goodbye to Lenny?
You're the fucking reason he's dead.
Let me tell you something, William.
It's a shit world out there.
You count on no one but yourself.
You either sink or you swim,
and, in Lenny's case,
he chose to sink.
You don't have the fucking right
to mention his name.
I fucking loved Lenny.
But he wasn't hard like you.
That's why you're still here
and he's dead, isn't it?
You beat the fucking shit out
of the both of us, didn't you?
Maybe I pushed you a bit hard.
But look at you.
- Get the fuck off...
- You afraid of anything?
No.
Are you the strongest bastard you know?
Yeah.
Tougher than I ever was.
Oh, you're welcome, asshole.
Yeah.
Lenny stuck that gun in his mouth
when you couldn't hack it anymore
and you pissed off to join
the SAS like a right cunt.
You're the one who abandoned him,
not me.
You're a fucking monster.
It takes one to know one.
Billy, for God's sake!
Pack it in! Pack it in!
Stop!
Jesus.
Christ, what have you done?
See?
Lenny could never have done that.
Christ. Billy.
Jesus.
All right, guys.
- Sorry, we gotta go.
- All right, guys. Thanks very much.
- Take care, God bless.
- God bless.
- I'm telling you... it's a mistake.
- What is?
Keeping fucking Starlight alive.
Hey. Yeah.
I underestimated her before.
I will not do it again.
"Starlight is a traitor"
is trending number one.
And we've got a million tweets
in support of Compound V.
A common enemy rallies the base.
Just trust me.
All right.
And if I can get my
hands on Hugh Campbell,
maybe pull his little spine out
the back of his fucking neck...
You okay?
Yeah, I just, um...
Your daughter?
Yeah.
80 years ago, she
looked exactly like that.
Sometimes it feels like yesterday.
I got something I want to show you.
What to finish up the backyard?
Okay if I put this person right there?
Hey, guys.
Hello.
This is Stormfront.
Stormfront, this is Rebecca.
Very nice to meet you.
And this is my son.
Hey, buddy. How you doing?
Listen, um...
I know, last time, uh,
I screwed up big-time, and, um...
and I just want you to
know I'm never, ever
gonna push you that hard again, okay?
All right, well, Ryan,
I'd love you to meet my
girlfriend, Stormfront.
Wow, he looks just like you.
You think?
Are you serious? Those eyes?
Hey, Ryan,
your daddy told me all about you.
- You have superpowers, huh?
- Mm-hmm.
That makes you very, very special.
You are the first
natural-born superhero.
Can we not?
That's right. Um...
Ryan does have powers,
but his mom doesn't like to
talk about them or use them.
Can you also let me know
before you just pop by?
He's Ryan's father.
He has a right to see his son.
Uh, that's very true, but, look,
we all just have Ryan's
best interests at heart.
- Right?
- Yes, we do.
I'm really sorry I haven't
been here enough.
Ryan, uh, I'd really like you
to get to know Stormfront.
I would. She's someone
I care about very much,
and, um...
I think you will, too.
So, I think, uh,
we'll be around more.
A lot more.
I want us to be a family.
Hey.
Empire Wok.
Hi.
That was a fraught "hi".
I'm going to my sister's for a while.
I have a plan.
You don't need to be
scared of Homelander.
That little girl...
on the plane.
What she must have gone through
in those last few moments.
I lie awake every night
thinking about that.
- Me, too.
- But then I start snowballing
and wondering... how many other people
have you killed and what
else have you done?
- I didn't have a choice.
- I'm not blaming you.
I'm not. It is not your fault.
Will you just... Will you
s... Will you sit down?
- And it's not fair.
- Will you sit down?
I wish I were as strong as you.
But I'm not.
I just need time.
Over and over, you...
You said you wanted to see the real me.
This is the real me.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Yes?
I'm here to see Jonah.
He's not taking any visitors.
Tell him it's Grace Mallory.
Goddamn.
We're on the wrong team.
Moral compromise
does have its privileges.
Grace.
I thought you retired.
Dr. Vogelbaum.
I thought you were taller.
Sonia, can you get some tea?
Thank you, but we won't
be staying long enough.
Ah, yes, there's that
WASPy patrician tone.
- All business.
- Doc, what do you know
about the Sage Grove Center?
Never heard of it. Should I have?
Considering Vought's been
doing illegal tests there
since you were the CSO
and they're still doing 'em to this day,
- seems like you should've.
- That's horrible.
Maybe it was Sonnenshine's
project over in R&D.
Prick always did have
a real god complex.
Do you recall the deal we made?
In exchange for me graciously dropping
certain involuntary
manslaughter charges?
I recall it was a long time ago.
Doesn't expire until the
statute of limitations does.
Then I guess I'm turning myself in.
We don't have to do this
dance anymore, Jonah.
We're both out.
Just a couple of retirees
shooting the shit on the back nine.
We both know Vought fucked you.
Probably put you in that chair.
Help us fuck 'em back.
Testify to Congress.
That's my daughter.
She took time off from her practice
to help a bitter old invalid.
I'm sorry to say this, Grace,
but you're the very last person
who should be asking me for help.
After what you lost.
Do what you like to me.
But some things are more
important than the right thing.
He's right, of course.
You should listen to him.
Ma'am?
Go back to your wife and daughter.
Nah. I'd just be putting
them in more danger.
Ah, yes,
the self-martyring bullshit
of the special ops soldier.
I'll get you all on a
flight to Nicaragua.
No one sees you again.
When this is done, I'll
take you up on that.
But that's the point,
Marvin. It's never done.
You just let go.
No justice for your father.
No revenge against Vought.
You get nothing,
except your family.
Go and never come back.
I wish I had.
An angry scene today
outside of Congresswoman
Victoria Neuman's residence,
as pro- and anti-Vought
protestors clashed
just two days before
the House Judiciary...
Another. And a pint of bitter.
M.M.
Yeah, good.
How'd it go with Vogelbaum?
I'll take care of it.
Send her back! Send her back!
Send her back! Send her
back! Send her back!
Life has always been hard,
but I don't remember
it being quite this crude.
I get it.
What she's doing with her daughter.
My papa... when he...
lost his mind,
my mama, she...
she kept me cooking with her.
Cassoulet, confit de canard,
all the mother sauces.
Cooking has, uh,
this way of giving port in a storm.
Did your...
your mama... she cook?
You know...
Irvin Yalom... he once
said you, you die twice.
Once, when you stop breathing,
and again when somebody...
utters your name for the last time.
I'd like to hear about your family.
Keep them alive a bit longer.
If you'd ever like to teach me.
Point is taken.
Never mind.
Gun?
I'm saying "gun"?
Très bien.
♪ That's the way, uh-huh,
uh-huh, I like it ♪
♪ Uh-huh, uh-huh, that's the way ♪
♪ Uh-huh, uh-huh ♪
♪ I like it, uh-huh, uh-huh ♪
♪ That's the way, uh-huh, uh-huh... ♪
- You're so cute.
♪ That's the way... ♪
- Hey, man. Hey.
- Hey! How's it going?
Good, good. Look, I
brought you something,
just to make up for all the
shit I used to do to you.
♪ Tell me I'm your loving man... ♪
He knows my name.
Yeah, okay.
Hey, meet my new bride
Cassandra. A-Train.
- Hi. It's nice to meet you.
- Hey. Nice to meet you, too.
- Thanks, man.
- Yeah.
No, it means a lot. It means a lot.
- Of course.
- A lot.
- Yeah, man.
Sweet.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey!
- Glad you came.
- Happy birthday.
- Good to see you, too.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, yeah.
- So...
great news.
I've got a meeting with
Stan Edgar next week.
- Wow.
- Seriously?
With Congress up their ass
and all the shit with Starlight,
Vought needs trusted,
proven commodities right now.
- They need you two.
- Yeah.
Still got a few deal
points to talk through,
but let's just say, they should
be getting your rooms ready.
- For real?
- Honey, this is amazing.
- Wow.
- Thank you. Thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
- This is awesome.
By the way, what do you guys
think of, um, Eagle the Archer?
Oh, he's like a brother to me.
Yeah, he was there for me
when I was at rock bottom.
He's the most kind, loving
person that you ever...
He's a toxic personality,
and no Church members are
to have any contact with him whatsoever.
Right. Yeah.
No, now that you mention it,
he did seem pretty toxic. Yeah.
Wh-What did he do?
Well, he claims the
program had failed him.
But actually he failed the program.
- He doesn't exist, you understand?
- Of course.
Ah. Oh, come on.
I think they're gonna do the limbo.
- Come on.
- Oh, yeah?
♪ That's the way, uh-huh, uh-huh ♪
♪ I like it, uh-huh, uh-huh ♪
♪ That's the way, uh-huh, uh-huh, I... ♪
Oh, me and Mr. Marathon used to
sneak college girls in this way.
College girls? Really?
They were applying. Yeah.
That does not make it better.
All right, moment of truth.
I'm either still in the system,
or we're about to be
swarmed by guards with AKs.
Wait. What?
And boom, bitches!
All right, let's go.
Maeve?
Hello?
What the fuck is this?!
This is not lesbian.
This is not on brand.
We need you ready for Congress
with Elena sitting proudly behind you.
She's gone.
- What do you mean, she's gone?
- Elena's gone.
Okay. Okay.
Elena will be back.
She will be back in your arms,
and you will be totally fine.
You're America's second-favorite
lesbian couple, after all.
You know what? Let's just
take a deep breath, okay?
Let's just... take a deep
breath here, okay?
We curated a coming-out
story that America loves,
- and it would be really good...
- Ashley.
For once in your life,
be a fucking human being.
I'm really sorry, Maeve.
Michael, that's holding!
We're in the middle of
practice, Leigh Anne. Ooh!
You can thank me later, Burt.
This team is your family, Michael.
Tony here is your quarterback.
You protect his blind side. Okay?
When you look at him, you think of me.
How you have my back, how you have his.
Okay?
Yes, ma'am.
Wow.
Uh... that...
th-that's really something, Ryan.
I've done "The Blind Side",
"Dances with Wolves",
"Terms of Endearment"...
all my mom's favorites.
So, are you into any
things that, you know,
kids are into?
Yeah.
Like, uh, NBA 2K?
PewDiePie?
What's that?
Or, uh, what about one
of your dad's movies?
You're in a movie?
I'm in a bunch of movies, man.
Uh, let's see, there's
"Homelander: Origins",
uh, "Homelander: Rise of a Hero",
"Homelander: Darkest Day",
- "Homelander: Brightest Night"...
- Oh, your dad is so good
- in "Homelander: Brightest Night".
- Thank you.
Mom, can I see them?
When you're old enough,
we can talk about it, okay?
Ah, they're PG. He can see them now.
You're old enough.
You're absolutely old enough.
For sleepovers and baseball games
- and visits to Vought Land.
- Yeah.
Did you know that your dad has
- his own roller coaster?
- Mm-hmm.
Do you want to take a ride
- on your dad's roller coaster?
- Can I, Mom?
We can talk about it.
Whenever you want.
I need to speak with you.
Eh, we're having a
good time here, right?
Outside.
Now.
That's a great idea.
You two... stay here, get
to know each other better.
Okay.
I'll show you, um, "Dances with Wolves".
- I know what you're doing.
- Nope, you don't.
- Yes, I do. I-I can see...
- No, you do not.
You could not possibly understand.
I was raised the same way as him.
That kid doesn't know
anything about anything.
When he sees the outside
world, he's going to panic.
Now, that's gonna fuck him up.
I do not want my son to have to
go through what I went through.
His life...
is different.
He has a mother.
And I know that that means
something to you. I do.
And if you take him
away from me, this...
this whole world will feel so confusing
- and frightening.
- Yes, but, Rebecca,
you... are lying to him.
Because I love him.
And I know a part of you loves him, too,
and that you want what's best for him.
But what's best for him is to be
here with me, with his mother.
Look, we have this opportunity
to give him a-a childhood you never had.
We can do that if he's here with me.
Please. I'm begging you, please.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
He's very tired.
I understand he's had
a few surprise visitors today.
But you tell him he's got one more.
The name's William Butcher.
Mr. Butcher, I can't apologize enough
for what I've done.
But I can't give you the information...
But I can't give you the information
you or Grace came for, either.
What was he like?
Who?
Homelander.
Growing up as a lad, what was he like?
I'm sure you don't want
to talk about this...
Oh, there is nothing I
want to talk about more.
And who knows better than you?
When he was a little boy, five or six,
he was quite sweet.
He'd cuddle up to me.
He loved stories about Davy Crockett,
Teddy Roosevelt.
Loved the idea of the woods, the forest,
manifest destiny.
Well, you know, I needed him to be
the strongest man in the world.
So I went to work on him.
He didn't even want it.
It was for me.
Hmm.
And that wasn't your only sin.
Was it?
It wasn't Homelander who hid
my wife away all them years.
It ever occur to you...
the pain you cause
sorry bastards like me?
At the time, it was barely
a blip on my radar.
Tell me, Doctor,
what's your radar telling you now?
Do what you want to me,
but I can't help you.
My family would be in...
Your family's already in trouble.
'Cause I'm about to go
into that room next door
to your daughter,
and I'm gonna bash her brains out.
And then I'm gonna find your
two sons and their wives
and their little kiddies.
Your whole fucking family dies today.
Or... you help me.
What's it gonna be, Doc?
How...?
How can...
can you be so...?
Oh, look at this.
Thank you.
Do you know...
I can't remember the last time
I had a good cup of char.
You're a doll.
You're starting to bleed through.
Ah, shit.
This is it, 42D.
And she's gonna be there?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What the hell? This is
the conference room.
She's not here.
They moved my statue?
What?
I wanted to do it in front of my statue.
Do what?
I just wanted to make my dad proud.
What the fuck?
What the fuck?!
Oh, oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Please evacuate to the
main floor immediately.
Mom!
Fuck you, man.
Shit, I need his hand.
Please evacuate to the
main floor immediately.
Huh?
Please evacuate to the
main floor immediately.
Come on, come on, come on.
Please evacuate to the
main floor immediately.
Was that an Almond Joy?
He has a tree nut allergy.
Come with me.
...to the main floor immediately.
Help! Is anybody there?!
Help!
Where's Annie?
Aren't you that sweaty
young man from Believe?
Hi, Mrs. January.
Is that a human hand?
Yes, it is. Come on. We got to go.
Hughie?
Annie! Annie! Annie!
- Oh, my God! Oh!
- Annie!
Hmm.
Oh!
Hey.
Wh-What are you doing here?
How are we gonna get out of here?
I know a way.
All right, dinner's ready!
Hey, bud. You ready for dinner?
What's wrong?
You're a liar.
- You lied to me.
- What do you mean?
They just flew me up and
showed me! This house is fake?
The neighbors are fake? You're fake?
Boy deserves to know the truth.
Hey. Listen to me.
We can talk about this, okay?
I know that you must feel confused,
and there are reasons
for what I did. I'm sorry.
No, just don't touch me! I hate you!
I think he just needs a little space.
- Come here, son.
- No. No.
All right, he needs his mother.
Don't worry. He'll still have a mother.
Hey, Ryan. Ryan!
Hey, Ryan, no!
Ryan! No!
Oh, my God. No. Please.
Kid, you are fucking unbelievable.
All you had to do was watch porn.
I didn't know he was
gonna set himself on fire.
- Hey.
- What the fuck are we gonna do now?
Butcher? It's me.
No, I'm afraid Hugh let our star
witness burn himself to death.
- Thank you.
- Well, I don't know.
What do you mean, no worries?
I mean, I've got it sorted.
You're gonna stitch me up again?
He's at the airport.
I promise.
You got a right bloody nerve, you do.
Ah, and I didn't mean
for it to go so bad.
I'm sorry.
You won't have to see him again.
He ain't got much longer.
Couple of months.
Tell me when it happens.
I'll piss on his coffin.
I didn't do it for him.
He's a cunt.
I just thought,
when you saw how helpless he is now...
you'd let it go.
He wouldn't have this hold over you,
and you wouldn't become like...
Yeah, well...
Mm.
I told 'em I wasn't gonna
cut my mama out of my life. That's it.
And then the Church and their
"Internal Research Bureau"
leaked all this [BLEEP] on me.
Eagle contends the Church released
a home video where his partner
was dressed as a deer
that Eagle hunted and mounted.
- What?
- Church spokeswoman
Carol Mannheim had this to say.
He has been spreading slanderous
and defamatory rumors about our religion
in a desperate attempt to stay relevant.
Yeah. Fuck him.
Thought he was your friend.
Hey, bartender, can we
just change the channel?
The hearing's almost on.
Thanks.
Internal investigations,
but we have also hired...
Would everybody please take your seats?
Starlight?
Um, nothing. She's off the grid.
- You fucking find her.
- Okay.
This bipartisan committee
is called to order,
investigating Vought International
and its production and
distribution of Compound V,
- which I hereby present...
- Okay.
- ...to the committee as evidence.
- This is it.
Mr. Chairman, if I may?
The testimony we're about
to hear today will prove
that Vought is guilty
of corporate malfeasance
and multiple felonies.
And it'll come from someone
that has witnessed
these crimes directly.
The chair calls former CSO of Vought,
Dr. Jonah Vogelbaum.
Okay, okay, quiet, everybody.
Quiet.
Got you, cunt.
Dr. Vogelbaum.
Thank you for joining us today.
Raise your right hand.
Do you swear that the testimony
you're about to give today
will be the truth, the whole
truth and nothing but the truth?
- I do.
- Thank you.
You have five minutes to
make your opening st...
- Oh!
- Oh, God!
Do something! What the fuck?!
Oh, shit.
What the fuck do we do now?
Sync & corrections by Costa Dax
www.addic7ed.com
♪ We're defended by our heroes ♪
♪ From sea to shining sea ♪
♪ Fighting for our freedom ♪
♪ Looking out for you and me ♪
♪ We think of all you gave us ♪
♪ How you were there to save us ♪
♪ So we'd see ♪
♪ You risked your life
so we could all live free ♪
♪ But our heroes ♪
♪ Never die ♪
♪ Your spirit fills the sky ♪
♪ Your presence truly
blessed us from the start ♪
♪ And you'll never truly
vanish from our hearts ♪
♪ And though my soul is aching ♪
♪ Deep inside, my heart is breaking ♪
♪ Nothing is the same
since you've been gone ♪
♪ No, I don't think I can take it ♪
♪ I don't know how I'll make it ♪
♪ When I'm beaten down
and think I can't go on ♪
♪ 'Cause our heroes ♪
♪ Never die ♪
♪ And the spirit fills the sky ♪
♪ Your presence truly
blessed us from the start ♪
♪ You'll never truly vanish ♪
♪ From our hearts. ♪
www.tvsubtitles.net