Sync & corrections by Costa Dax
www.addic7ed.com
They want us to believe that Vought
superheroes are the only answer.
What else are they lying to us about?
A-Train, you're out.
- Out of what?
- Out of the Seven.
I ended the relationship when I met you.
Stop fucking lying to me.
And you love her?
We shouldn't feel so calm or
safe. So, what are we gonna do?
Cross our fingers that
Homelander's gonna save us?
I'm the face of the Seven.
I'm just trying to help.
Ain't you supposed to be a hero?
I am a hero.
That's Liberty.
William Butcher?
I found Becca.
I'm gonna get you the fuck out of here.
- I'm not leaving.
- Becca, you and me...
- we could disappear.
- I have a son!
He's a fucking Supe freak.
Ruby!
Here! I'm here!
Looks like you saved me, Red.
No, you saved us.
If you hadn't broken into
that DHS mainframe...
True. I am a hell of a hacker...
but I'm no hero.
You are a hero in lots of ways.
What do you mean?
You're not afraid to live your life.
To be who you really are.
Me, I'm...
I'm afraid to... to show
the world who I am.
Yeah?
So who are you, Maeve?
I'm a lot like you.
I'm gay.
We have to keep moving.
And... cut!
Brilliant.
Yes, that was absolutely brilliant.
Gang, let's check that.
And, ladies and gents,
it is a wrap for today!
Good job, people.
That was so great.
Let's hit it hard in the
a.m., people, thank you.
That's a wrap, people!
Hey, Marty, play that back, please.
- You enjoying this?
- Yeah.
This new Joss rewrite really sings, huh?
When are you going to stop torturing me?
Don't know what you're talking about.
If I promise to never see her again,
will you stop?
But, Maeve, you're in love.
It's beautiful.
Elena's good for you,
and I'm not gonna let
you throw that away.
Not now, not ever.
I mean, that would be cruel.
- Can I have a word?
- Come on.
- Sir, please?
- Oh, look at this.
Look at these strong
female lesbians. Hmm?
I'm inspired.
- You inspired?
- Ooh, yeah.
Girls get it on.
Done. Girls get it done.
- They sure do, Ashley.
- In-in private.
Sir, please. It's urgent.
Ooh...
Ugh.
Terrific!
Oh.
So, what, they're all starving
but one of them's got
a fucking cell phone?
Uh, you know,
I really wish you had
cleared this with me
- before you went over there.
- Oh, Jesus Christ.
I don't have to clear
shit with you, Ashley.
I saw a chance for an
easy win, and I took it.
- How many views?
- Well, they posted last night,
we scrubbed it 17 minutes later.
But that's forever,
and there's been some-some blowback.
Blowback?
All right, fine, fine, fine.
So, what, I-I'm down a-a point?
Point and a half? Two?
No, nine and a half.
Nine and a half?
Nine... nine and a half?
Homelander kills!
What, th-they're fucking protesting...
- Homelander kills!
- ...me?
Oh, my God, th-they're pro...
they're protesting me?
They've been at the Tower all afternoon.
Why didn't you fucking say something?
Goddamn it.
Don't these fucking ingrates realize
I killed that asshole for them.
What do they think "Saving
America" fucking means, anyway?
Well, PR is drafting a
response as we speak.
Acknowledgment, apology, action.
No, no, no, no. Apology?
No.
You schedule a press conference,
and-and I'll clean it up myself.
Uh, well, Mr. Edgar...
and Legal would like
your official position
to be "no comment" at this time.
Please, no press
until the crisis team has
an actionable strategy.
Okay?
Bad day?
Hey, I'm with you.
Fuck these maxi
pad-wearing ingrate hicks,
but, you know, there's
a way to handle it.
I do not need your fucking help.
Sure. You seem to be
doing so well on your own.
Well, I'm here when you want me.
Hello, hello. Hughie?
Hey, hey. Hi, hi.
Sorry, thought, uh, I was
getting your voice mail.
That why you called five times?
No, I just thought you should know
Liberty, that Supe that
Raynor was looking into,
turns out it's Stormfront.
Vought changed her name,
they've been moving her around
like a fucking Catholic priest.
- Right.
- Um...
she probably murdered Raynor.
Annie's trying to figure out why, but...
you know, who the fuck knows.
Well...
as long as Starlight's on the job,
we're sorted then, yeah?
I'm not... I'm not mad, you know.
What you mean?
I-I just want you to know that, um...
yes, you are leaving us holding
the bag on this shitshow,
but I want you to know that I-I get it.
It's, uh, Becca.
I'd do the same thing.
I'm not mad.
Well...
wouldn't matter if you were.
Uh, how is she?
Lovelier than the day I met her.
Where are you?
Heading off grid.
Argentina, maybe.
Early retirement.
Butcher?
Yeah, what?
You could've said goodbye.
I know we've been through
some shit together.
You were...
you were always like
my canary, I suppose.
Thank you.
- Goodbye, Hughie.
- Your canary...
Hello?
On your feet, soldier.
Take me home to Lallybroch.
What are you watching?
A show called Eat My Dick.
Okay.
Have you seen Frenchie or Kimiko?
No. No, not... for a while. Why?
Fuck.
Uh, listen, I just got off
the phone with Butcher
and I think something might be wrong.
Like really, really wrong.
What would make you think that?
He was nice and...
...called me his canary?
Tell me everything he said.
Agent Pearson, sir.
Oh, you're a sight for sore eyes.
Agent Cruz, I thought we'd lost you.
I got by with a little
help from a friend.
Huh, so?
Good news or bad?
Yeah, I'd say that's good news.
And now the CG mutants approach.
And there's the bad news.
There's no way we can restore the grid
if we don't get that
flash drive to the Tower.
But how are you gonna
get through all of them?
Don't worry.
Girls get it done.
And cut on rehearsal. No one move.
- No one move. No one move.
- Cut on rehearsal!
- Starlight. I'm not touching.
- Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
- But can you just take a step?
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah, so keep going closer.
Can you mark her closer to Stormfront?
Let's mark her, please.
And let's just pretend...
like you like her, okay?
Okay, if I have to.
Okay. Okay, good stuff.
Let's try one for that. All right, good.
We should've shot that.
I mean, clearly you like me.
You've been eye-fucking me
like a lovesick stangirl all day.
Why is that?
I don't know. I think
that you're a good actor.
And I just, I feel like a
friggin' fembot up there.
You know...
Everybody, can we
please stand by to roll.
Let's try to make our day.
- How about that? Okay.
- Thank you.
♪ Extra, Extra. ♪
And turning now to superhero news,
former Seven member the Deep
surprised everybody last week
when he married Cassandra Schwartz,
an anthropology professor at Vassar,
in an intimate ceremony.
- Now, the couple has asked...
- Banana saltwater taffy.
God bless.
Ron can't live without it.
Billy?
- Hello, Judy.
- Who's this?
He's my nephew.
For Christ's sake, Billy,
you got to ring your mum.
Where's my boy?
Your mum and dad are
flying over, you know.
Your mum's worried to death about you.
No.
You tell 'em no.
It'd be a waste of a
perfectly good plane ticket.
Your father's quite ill.
The cancer's spreading fast.
Yeah, well, not fast enough.
I ain't seeing 'em. Now, where's me boy?
Oi, Terror.
You little rascal, eh?
Look at you, you little fucker.
You haven't changed a day.
How's about you and me go
for a little stroll then, eh?
Yeah?
Come on.
So this is what it all comes to, eh?
Metamucil and ringing our dicks
out for a few drops of piss.
I used to think that you, me and
Becca would grow old together.
Bloody stupid.
Turns out she don't...
What the fuck was any of it for?
Yes.
There he is, there's my guy.
Looking spectacular, as always.
- How we doing?
- Good.
- Feel good?
- Yeah. Uh...
Are you ready, huh?
You ready for this...
this big fucking scene today?
Yeah, well, that's-that's basically
what I wanted to talk to you about.
- Great. Yeah.
- 'Cause I did a little bit of a rewrite
and I want you to take a look.
Wow.
What a... lot of work.
Yeah, I...
I just felt like the dialogue
was a little... off.
You know, A-Train...
- would never say any of this shit.
- Right.
And you definitely just don't need that
giant expo dump at the end.
Your... big farewell speech?
Honestly, I think it's better if
we just leave it open-ended.
- Okay.
- You know what I mean?
Uh, where we can just play it in looks
and just not a whole bunch of words.
- Right.
- Maybe make it more of a question.
Like, is A-Train really
leaving the Seven?
- Yeah.
- We don't know.
Yeah.
Yeah, I think we're just gonna go ahead
and do the scene as scripted.
But thank you for putting
all this thought into it,
right, it shows you got a lot of heart.
Take that heart, put it in the scene.
All right, good stuff.
I'm not doing it.
I'm not doing this shitty scene.
Well...
That is way above my pay grade.
Bring that up with Ashley.
Right? Right.
Ooh, by the way.
I got the crew a Vietnamese crêpe truck.
They make a gluten-free banh xeo.
It is... fantastic.
You're going to be great, baby.
- Where are we going?
- Oh,
we need to see you in Wardrobe.
Deep.
You look so happy. I
hardly recognize you.
Katie, I'm in love, you know,
to an extraordinary woman
I'm now blessed to call my wife.
Ah, that-that's really nice.
Well, let's address the
elephant in the room.
Shall we?
Well, you know, I'm-I'm glad you asked,
because, uh, yeah, you know,
Kevin here has had
some issues in the past.
But people grow.
And if you could see the
letters that he writes me.
I mean, you would know
what a beautiful soul he has.
Oh, thank you.
Well, she's only saying that
'cause I make her
breakfast in bed, so...
- Oh, stop.
- French toast.
So, you are both members of
the Church of the Collective.
- Mm-hmm.
- It's not realistic.
Alexander Hamilton
wasn't no Puerto Rican.
That's the point.
It's a metaphor for the
immigrant experience in America.
But he was a white guy.
Ah.
You know what's really good?
Dear Evan Hansen.
Can we help you?
She's just a girl.
Show her a picture of
kittens or some shit.
How 'bout I show her
my motherfuckin' dick?
Bitch ain't right in the head.
Fuck!
Holy shit!
Merde.
Oi, Billy.
You should've told me you
were bringing company.
Oi, who's this one remind you of?
Isn't he the spitting of Lenny?
No.
Thought you were retiring.
Argentina, right?
I am.
What are you doing here?
Well, Hughie heard a
dog toy on the phone.
And I know you keep
Terror at your aunt's, so...
Brilliant as ever.
Time to go.
Come help us with Stormfront.
Came all this way for that, did you?
No, we... we came 'cause we're worried.
Your cunt sense tingling, is it?
Well, don't you worry... I'm sorted.
Where's Becca, man?
Becca?
What's he talking about?
Waiting for me at the Hampton Inn.
So...
lots of thanks, time to piss off.
We're not going anywhere.
Right.
Just so you know,
that's Terror's girlfriend.
- What?
- His fuck pig.
Black Noir's here.
What?
It wasn't us... we were cautious.
We swapped cars, no toll roads.
It's not you. It's me.
He must've tracked me from Becca's.
Billy, what's this all about?
It's complicated.
Becca's not with me.
You... couldn't get her out?
She didn't want out.
I'll explain everything,
but right now we're in
a little bit of trouble.
I'm sorry, Judy. I shouldn't have come.
Okay, maybe...
maybe we can make a run for it.
Just get to the car.
No, he moves faster than a car.
But if he wants to kill us...
he'll have to do it with an audience.
This is the fire department.
A natural gas leak has been reported.
Everyone out of your homes.
I repeat, a gas leak
has been reported...
Nice one, M.M.
Let's hope they stay a while.
Ma'am, do you have
any nails, ball bearings,
electrical wiring,
pressurized aerosol products.
I need a can about this big.
Really appreciate it.
Team Britney, 2007.
Remember the meltdown?
Oh, ooh, yeah, that...
But, you know...
You're a firecracker.
- Mom?
- Oh, hi.
Annie.
Oh, you-you-you look so pretty.
What...?
- What are you doing here?
- I-I'm in town.
I've been texting you for days.
I-I-I wasn't trying to
ambush you, I promise.
Did you get any of the
Vietnamese crêpes?
'Cause they're dope.
No, no, no, I'm good. Thanks.
Your mom was telling me
about the hero pageants you used to do.
Lucky.
My mom would never let me.
Adele did not go in
for that sort of thing.
I had to do all my speeches
to a brush in the mirror.
I like this one.
Mom, this isn't a great time.
I-I know that you're busy,
but you don't have to
entertain me, I promise.
I-I wanted to see you, sweetheart.
I... I miss you.
I think that this is something
that we need to discuss in private.
Donna, can I tell her?
- Tell me what?
- Look, your mom
is so sorry about the Compound V,
and she understands that
keeping that a secret
really hurt your relationship.
Yeah, and that I-I used you as a trophy
to make myself feel important.
I know that now.
Why are you talking to a
stranger about our relationship?
She's not a stranger.
She's your teammate.
Annie, the-the whole world
knows about Compound V.
I mean, lots of parents did what I did.
I... I'm hoping that you'll...
that you'll forgive me.
Please forgive me, Annie.
This is not the time
or the place for this.
Look, everyone is upset
about Compound V.
I mean, someone was so upset,
they leaked it to the press.
Can you imagine how
angry that person is?
Whoever they are?
I'll let you two hash it
out, but I just think...
if it was me, I'd be grateful
to have a mom like Donna.
Honey, please?
I need to get back to set.
Do you need someone to
drive you back to your hotel?
No, I'll-I'll-I'll get a cab.
Okay.
Okay,
now, Queen Maeve, a goddess,
but our Empress of the
Otherworld struggles inside.
Questions of identity
rock her to her core.
- Until she meets...
- Elena.
The connection is
immediate, all-consuming.
A sweet sapphic love blossoms,
raising Maeve's consciousness
and revealing her own inner truth.
She's gay, and it's okay.
- It's...
- Powerful.
She's more than just a superhero now.
She is a symbol.
Representation matters.
She's #BraveMaeve.
We're recommending a
multipronged image makeover.
First, guest spots on Queer Eye.
Then, an exclusive "It Gets Better" PSA.
Kimberly Peirce might direct.
Grand marshals at the New
York and Chicago Pride,
because you are two proud lesbians.
You know Maeve is bi, right?
Yeah, you know what?
I just feel like lesbian is
a bit of an easier sell.
A bit more cut-and-dry.
- Now, for Elena...
- Me?
You're going to love it, yeah.
Why am I a part of this shit?
We are going with a
polished, tailored look.
- That looks like menswear.
- Pew research shows
that two feminine
women in a relationship
sends a problematic message.
Yeah, this isn't Penthouse Forum.
Americans are more accepting of gays
when they're in a clear-cut
gender role relationship.
- Like Ellen and Portia.
- Okay.
Let's get one thing straight.
I have no interest in being
in a public relationship.
Oh, you will be compensated.
I am not for sale.
Really?
You're not going to say anything?
- I'll fix this.
- Yeah.
Elena.
Elena, wait.
If they want a lesbian Ken doll,
they can find someone else.
I am going to cash in my vacation days
and go stay with my sister.
No. You can't do that.
Why? I'm not under contract.
This is Homelander.
Okay? And he's fucking with me.
And if you go out there,
Elena, there is nowhere you
can go that he won't find you.
Please.
Stay.
I can't protect you if you leave.
But what are we gonna do?
We're gonna take that motherfucker down.
- You trust me?
- Yeah.
Okay.
Is this right?
Just like Home Alone
except way less delightful.
Butcher?
No.
It ain't right.
What's going on?
That ninja cunt's here for me, isn't he?
Yeah, but you can't go
out there... he'll kill you.
So...
So that's it?
Expecting a happy ending, were we?
Well, I'm sorry, Hughie.
It ain't that kind of massage parlor.
Now, I can keep him busy
for a little while, yeah?
Give you lot a chance to leg it.
I'm knackered.
I could use a little lie-down.
Fuck you.
What, am I supposed to be impressed
by this blaze of glory jerk-off shit?
Guess not.
You don't think I thought
about cashing it in after Robin?
'Cause I do.
Still.
A lot.
But I don't.
And the thing that kills me
is that your wife is alive.
She just doesn't want you, that's all.
Say that again.
So you don't have shit.
Welcome to the fucking club.
I mean, come on, what do, what
do any of us have besides...?
Who the fuck asked you to come here?
Eh?
I don't need your help.
Jesus, you're fucking pathetic.
You're so scared of being alone, Hughie.
First you latch onto Robin,
then Starlight, and now me.
Well, you know what, son?
I ain't interested.
Look, just get out of the fucking way.
Don't make me move you.
You can move him,
but good luck with me.
Que se passe-t-il ?
She wanted the job.
You have her doing hits?
The Albanians have her doing hits.
I'm just a girl getting ten percent.
- You...
- I'm sorry, pumpkin,
but I told you,
she's no kitten.
She can make her own choices.
Why?
How is this stopping Stormfront?
I know you blame
yourself for your brother,
I know the rage you feel,
but this... this is not the way.
This is poison for your soul.
I know.
Come with me, mon coeur.
I got my own baby brother killed!
He was the only thing
that mattered to me!
Stop trying to help me!
I don't want your help!
I don't understand what you're saying
because you won't teach me!
Fuck this.
Fuck you.
Go be a monster.
Remember when you were young
and the world was full of possibilities?
Before all the mistakes,
heartbreaks and disappointments?
What if you could go back
to the way things were?
I used to be angry, insecure and unsure.
But thanks to the
Church of the Collective,
I now know the kind of man I want to be.
The kind of man who calls out injustice
- when he sees it.
- Stop.
- Come on.
- Hey, dude.
That's not cool.
The kind of man who
stands up for what's right.
Come on, guys, knock it off.
The kind of man who sees
the potential in all of us.
So join us at the Church
of the Collective,
and be the person you
were always meant to be.
That's a bunch of bullshit.
Didn't used to be.
Church used to mean something.
Oh, what, are you a member?
I was, long time ago.
Hmm.
That place used to be pure.
And then they just started
letting all kinds of people in,
you know?
I don't know.
So, why don't you tell me?
Well, I think you do know.
Some people are quality
and others are...
garbage.
We are rolling.
Oh, by the way,
I heard they're retiring you?
So unfair.
Do you have a problem?
Of course not. Why would you say that?
Can I have a word? Please?
Adam tells me you don't
want to do the scene.
I just can't be a part of
something I don't believe in.
Look, I know it's not easy
losing your job. Okay?
When I got fired, I tindered
my way through Barcelona.
Everyone in that city ate my paella.
Fucked a guy with elephantiasis.
But I got through it, and so will you.
Yeah, but I'm still making it happen.
I mean, my A-Trainers sell how
many fucking pairs per year?
Look on the bright side...
you served four years
longer than Mr. Marathon.
Now, that is something, okay.
But... please.
Let me just... talk to Homelander.
We both know that's not a good idea.
I'm sorry.
I'm not saying the lines.
Okay, this can go one of two ways.
One: You leave the
Seven with your dignity
and your severance package intact.
Or two: You get fired
for breaching your morality clause
by shooting up Compound V
and giving yourself a
fucking heart attack
in the fucking process.
It's your choice.
You know, the truth is...
I've been running my whole life.
Think it's time that I
stay put for a while.
It's time I went home.
I know this is dawn of the Seven.
But it's sunset on A-Train.
It's been a good run.
Cut!
Hey, dude. That was awesome.
Awesome? A-Dog, that was fucking gold.
Buddy, look, I'm ready to
move on, but how do you feel?
You want another one? Just let me know.
No, man, go ahead and move on.
All right, check it! Moving on!
Tiffany, we need you over at Mo-cap.
- Good day.
- Yeah, going over there now.
Yes, it's true.
Vought has all the money and the power.
And we have, no offense, jack shit.
We love you, Victoria!
But after Homelander's war crime...
...how can I stay quiet
and still look my daughter in the eyes?
I can't. I know you can't.
And guess what.
The House Judiciary can't either!
Finally!
We are going to hold hearings
on Vought and Compound V!
Yes! Yes!
Hey, everyone.
May I?
Thank you.
Congresswoman Neuman, everybody.
Isn't she great? Didn't
you love that little
"Walk Like an Egyptian"
dance she did online?
So fun.
I loved it.
But fun is not what
we're here for, is it?
- No, no, no, no, no, fuck.
- Let me just start by saying
how pleased I am to see you all here.
Everyone get the fuck
out! Get the fuck out!
- Fuck you. Get out.
- ...that we live in a country
where all your voices can be heard.
I know that some of
you are a little upset
by that video online of me
stopping the terrorist,
and I just want you to
know that I understand.
I'm upset, too.
I mean, come on, guys.
Nobody wants innocent
people to get hurt.
Of course not.
But sadly,
well, the bad guys,
they don't think like us.
And so, sometimes...
well, these things just happen.
Wait, this happened before?
- How many times?
- Well, no, h-hold on, guys.
My point is, we all have
the same goals, don't we?
- To keep our country safe.
- No.
So American lives are the
only ones worth protecting?
Of course not.
But if you've served with our
amazing soldiers, like I have,
you would know that
freedom comes at a price.
You don't speak for us!
Yeah, you don't speak for us!
- You don't speak for us!
All right, all right.
Everyone just calm down.
Calm down. Let's not let your hearts
- get in the way of your heads.
- You don't speak for us!
You don't speak for us!
- Everyone just relax.
- You don't speak for us!
You don't speak for us!
- Calm down.
- You don't speak for us!
You don't speak for us!
- Fuck Homelander!
All right.
You guys are the real heroes.
God bless you!
Love you guys!
You don't speak for us!
You guys are all good.
- Oh, thank you.
- Thank you.
- It's time.
- Right, lads.
To the taffy room.
This is bollocks.
This is the taffy room?
An affordable alternative
to privatized health care.
She's a dealer.
All right, everyone just calm down.
Calm down. Let's not let your hearts...
Oh, you fucking...
You guys, you're the real heroes.
You fucking...
Fuck, fuck. Fuck!
No one ever said the job was easy.
Look, he's just a kid.
17 years old. You don't
got to look him in the face.
Look, no one's ever achieved
anything without sacrifice.
The kid's a hero.
Think of it like that.
Right. A hero.
Okay.
Come in!
Where do you get all these?
Oh, this is just the first batch.
I'll have Logan punch up the fear.
Logan?
My meme-queen.
- Hmm.
- So...
when you see it on your
uncle's Facebook page,
then you know it's working.
Hmm.
Um...
can I ask you something?
Well, suppose I got the time.
Who's Lenny?
You said I looked like him?
Oh.
Billy wouldn't want me to say.
Fuck Billy.
Lenny's his little brother.
Uh, Butcher... has a brother?
Yeah.
Skinny, nervous little bugger.
Like you.
Fourth grade.
Little wanker named Dorian Savory
breaks Lenny's nose.
Oh, Billy goes to work on him.
Was bringing the see-saw down
on Dorian's noggin, wham, wham!
Probably gonna top him.
Kids, teachers trying
to drag Billy away,
but no... no good, not gonna happen,
Dorian's a goner.
And then Lenny steps in,
face all bleeding, and leads Billy away
easy, quiet as a lamb.
That was Lenny.
He had a way of making Billy not be...
well, you know... Billy.
I think Billy needs someone
like that, you know?
Where's Lenny now?
Oh, God rest his soul.
What happened?
Whoa-whoa-whoa...
Easy, easy, Terror, easy. Easy.
M.M.! Come on, everybody, out!
Out the side door!
Move!
Butcher.
Get 'em out of here.
Butcher, wait, wait, wait!
What are you...?
Butcher! Butcher!
Butcher, what are you doing?!
Butcher, you don't...
Don't do this!
Butcher!
All right, you fucker.
Where are you?
So you want to take me on, do you?
Think you got the bollocks?
Well, come on, then...
cunt.
What the fuck are you doing?!
Get out of here!
Oi, gimp cunt!
Over here, gimp cunt!
I'm the one you want. Come here!
You kill him...
and you can kiss your
fucking career goodbye.
I got photos...
of Vought's dirty little secret...
my wife's son...
Homelander's son.
Now, you lay one fucking finger
on any of us,
and those photos go out of the cloud
and into Ronan Farrow's inbox.
And then the whole world will know
that Homelander is nothing
but a filthy fucking rapist
and Vought has been hiding
his little laser-eyed bastard.
Now, you cunts went to a lot of
trouble to keep that a secret.
I reckon you might want
to keep it that way.
♪ Halle... ♪
Mr. Butcher.
- Oh, hello, cunt.
- How can I be sure
you actually have the
proof of which you speak?
You can't.
Roll the dice, cunt.
I reckon he'd be more popular
than Meghan and Harry's little sprog.
Here's my first and final offer.
That information never
sees the light of day,
and I'll call off Black Noir.
All right.
You got yourself a deal.
Want to shake on it?
Put Noir on.
Oi, missus wants a word.
Jesus Christ, Billy.
- M.M., you all right?
- I'm okay.
Do you really have those pictures?
Of course I do.
They said there'd be food.
Well, this is food for your soul.
Go with love.
All right.
Hi.
Maeve, oh, my God. Hi.
- What brought you here?
- Oh!
Wait, are you...?
Uh... do you want to check this out?
- Oh, fuck no. No.
- Okay.
Listen, uh, we should talk.
Yeah.
If any of these Moonies
are gonna help you
get back in the Seven,
and that's a big if,
then you're gonna need a woman to...
tell everyone that you're
not a complete piece of shit.
I could be that person for you.
Wait, you think I'm a piece of shit?
Fuck yeah.
The point is, I can help you.
If you help me.
- Hmm.
- Yeah,
I've got Stormfront. Flying in.
I'll take the goi cuon.
Nah, no, the bun cha.
Does that have peppers?
Thank you.
What are you doing in my trailer?
You know, you had no right
to talk to my mother
about personal shit.
What were you trying to prove?
Okay, sorry. Just trying to help.
She didn't just lie to me
about Compound V, okay?
She lied to me about everything.
So don't try and broker some
kind of peace between us,
because I don't want it.
Wow, that-that...
I mean...
that...
is a performance.
Oh, my God, look, I'm, like, tearing up.
You don't suck, Starlight.
You are Tilda fucking Swinton.
I know you leaked it.
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
Not as good.
Magic's gone.
I guess lightning really
doesn't strike twice, huh?
Okay, whatever. You know what?
I need to get to set, so...
That hack-a-limb Gecko,
yeah, he stole the V and then you...
you leaked it to MSNBC.
Now, what do you think Vought's
gonna feel when I tell them?
Well, how do you think
the world will feel
when I tell 'em that
you used to be Liberty?
Wow.
You are a special kind
of poison flower, huh,
going against your own people?
You mean fucking white people?
Starlight.
Superheroes.
Don't be racist.
Oh, my.
Oh, yes.
That is adorable.
I do like you.
You... you got spunk.
You're gonna be a big help to me.
What the hell does that mean?
Come in!
Hello, you two.
Not interrupting, am I?
No.
Just between us girls, right, Starlight?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's right.
- See you around.
- Mm-hmm.
Can't wait to shoot our scene together.
Yeah, me, too.
What was that all about?
Are you girls friendly?
No, just running lines.
What's up?
Uh...
me.
- Five points.
- Ah.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, people are, uh, checking boxes
like "patriotic"
and, uh... "unwavering".
I owe you.
Well, what are you ever
gonna do to repay me?
Well...
here we are.
I'm sorry.
I almost threw in the
towel like a bleeding twat.
We're harder than that, isn't we?
I will get your mum back.
I swear to God, I'll get your mum back.
Just take a little bit longer.
You hang in there. All right?
You be a good boy for Judy.
Yeah, that's a good lad.
Oh.
I almost forgot.
I got you something.
Terror...
...fuck it.
That's my boy.
I'll always protect you.
Mmm.
You're all right
- for an old bat.
- Yeah, yeah.
Let's go.
♪ Every time ♪
♪ That I look in the mirror ♪
♪ All these lines on my
face getting clearer ♪
♪ The past is gone ♪
♪ It went by ♪
♪ Like dusk to dawn ♪
♪ Isn't that the way ♪
♪ Everybody's got their dues ♪
♪ In life to pay ♪
Do it. You know you want to.
I'll cut you in half.
Come on.
Right here.
Don't be a pussy...
laser my fucking tits.
Ow.
Oh, God, it fucking hurts.
Don't stop.
See?
I told you I don't break easy.
♪ Yeah, sing with me ♪
♪ Sing for the year ♪
♪ Sing for the laughter,
sing for the tear ♪
♪ Sing with me, it's just for today ♪
♪ Maybe tomorrow the good
Lord will take you away ♪
♪ Mm, dream on ♪
♪ Dream on, dream on ♪
♪ Dream until your dream come true ♪
Sync & corrections by Costa Dax
www.addic7ed.com
♪ Dream on, dream on, dream on ♪
♪ Dream until your dream come true ♪
♪ Dream on, dream on,
dream on, dream on ♪
♪ Dream on, dream on, dream on ♪
♪ Oh... ♪
♪ Dream on, dream on,
dream on, dream on ♪
♪ Dream on, dream on, dream on ♪
♪ Oh... ♪
♪ Sing with me, sing for the year ♪
♪ Sing for the laughter,
sing for the tear ♪
♪ Sing with me, it's just for today ♪
♪ Maybe tomorrow the good
Lord will take you away ♪
♪ Sing with me, sing for the year ♪
♪ Sing for the laughter,
sing for the tear ♪
♪ Sing with me, it's just for today ♪
♪ Maybe tomorrow the good
Lord will take you away. ♪
www.tvsubtitles.net